<Collection>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>1</DOCNO>
		<Title>Neon Prey (A Prey Novel) Hardcover </Title>
		<Author>John Sandford</Author>
		<Cover>cover_1</Cover>
		<Text>
			Clayton Deese looks like a small-time criminal, muscle for hire when his loan shark boss needs to teach someone a lesson. Now, seven months after a job that went south and landed him in jail, Deese has skipped out on bail, and the U.S. Marshals come looking for him. They don't much care about a low-level guy--it's his boss they want--but Deese might be their best chance to bring down the whole operation. Then, they step onto a dirt trail behind Deese's rural Louisiana cabin and find a jungle full of graves. Now Lucas Davenport is on the trail of a serial killer who has been operating for years without notice. His quarry is ruthless, and--as Davenport will come to find--full of surprises
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>2</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Mother-in-Law</Title>
		<Author>Sally Hepworth</Author>
		<Cover>cover_2</Cover>
		<Text>
			A twisty, compelling new novel about one woman's complicated relationship with her mother-in-law that ends in death. From the moment Lucy met her husband’s mother, she knew she wasn’t the wife Diana had envisioned for her perfect son. Exquisitely polite, friendly, and always generous, Diana nonetheless kept Lucy at arm’s length despite her desperate attempts to win her over. And as a pillar in the community, an advocate for female refugees, and a woman happily married for decades, no one had a bad word to say about Diana…except Lucy. That was five years ago. Now, Diana is dead, a suicide note found near her body claiming that she longer wanted to live because of the cancer wreaking havoc inside her body. But the autopsy finds no cancer. It does find traces of poison, and evidence of suffocation. Who could possibly want Diana dead? Why was her will changed at the eleventh hour to disinherit both of her children, and their spouses? And what does it mean that Lucy isn’t exactly sad she’s gone? Fractured relationships and deep family secrets grow more compelling with every page in this twisty, captivating new novel from Sally Hepworth.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>3</DOCNO>
		<Title>Saman</Title>
		<Author>Ayu Utami</Author>
		<Cover>cover_3</Cover>
		<Text>
			Saman is a story filtered through the lives of its feisty female protagonists and the enigmatic “hero” Saman. It is at o­nce an exposé of the oppression of plantation workers in South Sumatra, a lyrical quest to understand the place of religion and spirituality in contemporary lives, a playful exploration of female sexuality and a story about love in all its guises, while touching o­n all of Indonesia’s taboos: extramarital sex, political repression and the relationship between Christians and Muslims. Saman has taken the Indonesian literary world by storm and sold over 100,000 copies in the Indonesian language, and is now available for the first time in English.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>4</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Overstory</Title>
		<Author>Richard Powers</Author>
		<Cover>cover_4</Cover>
		<Text>
			An Air Force loadmaster in the Vietnam War is shot out of the sky, then saved by falling into a banyan. An artist inherits a hundred years of photographic portraits, all of the same doomed American chestnut. A hard-partying undergraduate in the late 1980s electrocutes herself, dies, and is sent back into life by creatures of air and light. A hearing- and speech-impaired scientist discovers that trees are communicating with one another. These four, and five other strangers―each summoned in different ways by trees―are brought together in a last and violent stand to save the continent’s few remaining acres of virgin forest. In his twelfth novel, National Book Award winner Richard Powers delivers a sweeping, impassioned novel of activism and resistance that is also a stunning evocation of―and paean to―the natural world. From the roots to the crown and back to the seeds, The Overstory unfolds in concentric rings of interlocking fables that range from antebellum New York to the late twentieth-century Timber Wars of the Pacific Northwest and beyond, exploring the essential conflict on this planet: the one taking place between humans and nonhumans. There is a world alongside ours―vast, slow, interconnected, resourceful, magnificently inventive, and almost invisible to us. This is the story of a handful of people who learn how to see that world and who are drawn up into its unfolding catastrophe.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>5</DOCNO>
		<Title>Cemetery Road</Title>
		<Author>Greg Iles</Author>
		<Cover>cover_5</Cover>
		<Text>
			When Marshall McEwan left his Mississippi hometown at eighteen, he vowed never to return. The trauma that drove him away spurred him to become one of the most successful journalists in Washington, DC. But as the ascendancy of a chaotic administration lifts him from print fame to television stardom, Marshall discovers that his father is terminally ill, and he must return home to face the unfinished business of his past. On arrival, he finds Bienville, Mississippi very much changed.  His family’s 150-year-old newspaper is failing; and Jet Turner, the love of his youth, has married into the family of Max Matheson, one of a dozen powerful patriarchs who rule the town through the exclusive Bienville Poker Club.  To Marshall’s surprise, the Poker Club has taken a town on the brink of extinction and offered it salvation, in the form of a billion-dollar Chinese paper mill.  But on the verge of the deal being consummated, two murders rock Bienville to its core, threatening far more than the city’s economic future. An experienced journalist, Marshall has seen firsthand how the corrosive power of money and politics can sabotage investigations. Joining forces with his former lover—who through her husband has access to the secrets of the Poker Club—Marshall begins digging for the truth behind those murders.  But he and Jet soon discover that the soil of Mississippi is a minefield where explosive secrets can destroy far more than injustice.  The South is a land where everyone hides truths: of blood and children, of love and shame, of hate and murder—of damnation and redemption.  The Poker Club’s secret reaches all the way to Washington, D.C., and could shake the foundations of the U.S. Senate.  But by the time Marshall grasps the long-buried truth about his own history, he would give almost anything not to have to face it.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>6</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Storyteller's Secret</Title>
		<Author>Sejal Badani</Author>
		<Cover>cover_6</Cover>
		<Text>
			Nothing prepares Jaya, a New York journalist, for the heartbreak of her third  miscarriage and the slow unraveling of her marriage in its wake. Desperate to  assuage her deep anguish, she decides to go to India to uncover answers to her  family’s past. Intoxicated by the sights, smells, and sounds she experiences, Jaya becomes an  eager student of the culture. But it is Ravi—her grandmother’s former servant  and trusted confidant—who reveals the resilience, struggles, secret love, and  tragic fall of Jaya’s pioneering grandmother during the British occupation.  Through her courageous grandmother’s arrestingly romantic and heart-wrenching  story, Jaya discovers the legacy bequeathed to her and a strength that, until  now, she never knew was possible.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>7</DOCNO>
		<Title>Watchmen: The Deluxe Edition (Watchmen)</Title>
		<Author>Dave Gibbons</Author>
		<Cover>cover_7</Cover>
		<Text>
			In an alternate world where the mere presence of American superheroes changed history, the US won the Vietnam War, Nixon is still president, and the cold war is in full effect. WATCHMEN begins as a murder-mystery, but soon unfolds into a planet-altering conspiracy. As the resolution comes to a head, the unlikely group of reunited heroes--Rorschach, Nite Owl, Silk Spectre, Dr. Manhattan and Ozymandias--have to test the limits of their convictions and ask themselves where the true line is between good and evil. In the mid-eighties, Alan Moore and Dave Gibbons created WATCHMEN, changing the course of comics' history and essentially remaking how popular culture perceived the genre. Popularly cited as the point where comics came of age, WATCHMEN's sophisticated take on superheroes has been universally acclaimed for its psychological depth and realism.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>8</DOCNO>
		<Title>Twisted Prey (A Prey Novel) Paperback</Title>
		<Author>Lucas Davenport</Author>
		<Cover>cover_8</Cover>
		<Text>
			A rich psychopath, Taryn Grant had run successfully for the U.S. Senate, where  Lucas had predicted she'd fit right in. He was also convinced that she'd been  responsible for three murders, though he'd never been able to prove it. Once a  psychopath had gotten that kind of rush, though, he or she often needed another  fix, so he figured he might be seeing her again. He was right. A federal marshal now, with a very wide scope of investigation,  he's heard rumors that Grant has found her seat on the Senate intelligence  committee, and the contacts she's made from it, to be very...useful. Pinning  those rumors down was likely to be just as difficult as before, and considerably  more dangerous. But they had unfinished business, he and Grant. One way or the other, he was  going to see it through to the end.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>9</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Trouble With Vampires</Title>
		<Author>Lynsay Sands</Author>
		<Cover>cover_9</Cover>
		<Text>
			For close to three thousand years the imposing, impossibly handsome Santo Notte has fought in armies across the world and battled his own, more personal enemies. Of all the places he might expect to encounter his life mate, a quiet corner of upstate New York doesn’t seem likely. But as soon as he makes contact with history professor Petronella Stone, while hunting down a suspected rogue immortal, he knows that she will be the greatest adventure of his eternal life. He expects her to be surprised, confused, even overwhelmed. What he doesn’t expect is that Pet has a secret history of her own. There’s no mistaking the mind-blowing, mutual pleasure they share. But as Pet struggles to protect her nephew from a danger lurking too close to home, Santo realizes there’s another threat to her safety—him. And claiming their passionate future will be impossible until he leaves his past behind, forever.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>10</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Binding</Title>
		<Author>Bridget Collins</Author>
		<Cover>cover_10</Cover>
		<Text>
			"A rich, gothic entertainment that explores what books have trapped inside them and reminds us of the power of storytelling. Spellbinding.” — TRACY CHEVALIER Imagine you could erase grief. Imagine you could remove pain. Imagine you could hide the darkest, most horrifying secret. Forever. Young Emmett Farmer is working in the fields when a strange letter arrives summoning him away from his family. He is to begin an apprenticeship as a Bookbinder—a vocation that arouses fear, superstition, and prejudice amongst their small community, but one neither he nor his parents can afford to refuse. For as long as he can recall, Emmett has been drawn to books, even though they are strictly forbidden. Bookbinding is a sacred calling, Seredith informs her new apprentice, and he is a binder born. Under the old woman’s watchful eye, Emmett learns to hand-craft the elegant leather-bound volumes. Within each one they will capture something unique and extraordinary: a memory. If there’s something you want to forget, a binder can help. If there’s something you need to erase, they can assist. Within the pages of the books they create, secrets are concealed and the past is locked away. In a vault under his mentor’s workshop rows upon rows of books are meticulously stored. But while Seredith is an artisan, there are others of their kind, avaricious and amoral tradesman who use their talents for dark ends—and just as Emmett begins to settle into his new circumstances, he makes an astonishing discovery: one of the books has his name on it. Soon, everything he thought he understood about his life will be dramatically rewritten.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>11</DOCNO>
		<Title>Revenge of the Zombie Monks: An Unofficial Graphic Novel for Minecrafters</Title>
		<Author>Cara J. Stevens</Author>
		<Cover>cover_11</Cover>
		<Text>
			Phoenix, Wolfie, and their friends are back in this exciting second part of the Unofficial Graphic Novel for Minecrafters series! Past the walls of their monastery, the monks of Xenos grow enchanted golden apples for their neighbor villagers. As readers learn in Quest for the Golden Apple, these golden apples have magical healing abilities and have the power to keep the villagers save. The monks also have and protect the knowledge that connects Xenos to her sister worlds. This knowledge keeps Xenos and her citizens safe. But when the monks are zombified, Xenos’s citizens need a new hero.  Following the design of zombie comics and Minecraft comics, follow Phoenix and her friends as they fight to save the citizens and monks of Xenos. But Phoenix and her crew of heroes have no idea and do not suspect the culprit behind this disaster—an incredibly powerful foe who will do anything to keep Phoenix from saving her world.  The following three books in this series—Chasing Herobrine, The Ender Eye Prophecy, and Battle for the Dragon’s Temple—continue the adventures of Phoenix and are written by Cara J. Stevens. This book is sure to delight fans of both authors, graphic novels, and Minecraft. Sky Pony Press, with our Good Books, Racehorse and Arcade imprints, is proud to publish a broad range of books for young readers—picture books for small children, chapter books, books for middle grade readers, and novels for young adults. Our list includes bestsellers for children who love to play Minecraft; stories told with LEGO bricks; books that teach lessons about tolerance, patience, and the environment, and much more. In particular, this adventure series is created especially for readers who love the fight of good vs. evil, magical academies like Hogwarts in the Harry Potter saga, and games like Minecraft, Terraria, and Pokemon GO. While not every title we publish becomes a New York Times bestseller or a national bestseller, we are committed to books on subjects that are sometimes overlooked and to authors whose work might not otherwise find a home.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>12</DOCNO>
		<Title>Ursula K. Le Guin: The Hainish Novels and Stories: A Library of America Boxed Set</Title>
		<Author>Ursula K. Le Guin</Author>
		<Cover>cover_12</Cover>
		<Text>
			In such visionary masterworks as the Nebula and Hugo Award winners The Left Hand of Darkness and The Dispossessed, Ursula K. Le Guin redrew the map of modern science fiction, imagining a galactic confederation of human colonies founded by the planet Hain, an array of worlds whose divergent societies—the result of both evolution and genetic engineering—allow her to speculate on what is intrinsic in human nature. Now, for the first time, the complete Hainish novels and stories are collected in a deluxe two-volume Library of America boxed set, with new introductions by the author. Volume one gathers the first five Hainish novels: Rocannon’s World, in which an ethnologist sent to a bronze-age planet must help defeat an intergalactic enemy; Planet of Exile, the story of human colonists stranded on a planet that is slowly killing them; City of Illusions, which finds a future Earth ruled by the mysterious Shing; and the Hugo and Nebula Award-winning masterpieces The Left Hand of Darkness and The Dispossessed—as well as four short stories. Volume two presents Le Guin’s final two Hainish novels, The Word for World Is Forest, in which Earth enslaves another planet to strip its natural resources, and The Telling, the harrowing story of a society which has suppressed its own cultural heritage. Rounding out the volume are seven short stories and the story suite Five Ways to Forgiveness, published here in full for the first time.  The endpapers feature Le Guin's own hand-drawn map of Gethen, the planet that is the setting for The Left Hand of Darkness, and a full-color chart of the known worlds of Hainish descent. LIBRARY OF AMERICA is an independent nonprofit cultural organization founded in 1979 to preserve our nation’s literary heritage by publishing, and keeping permanently in print, America’s best and most significant writing. The Library of America series includes more than 300 volumes to date, authoritative editions that average 1,000 pages in length, feature cloth covers, sewn bindings, and ribbon markers, and are printed on premium acid-free paper that will last for centuries.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>13</DOCNO>
		<Title>Hellbent: An Orphan X Novel</Title>
		<Author>Gregg Hurwitz</Author>
		<Cover>cover_13</Cover>
		<Text>
			Taken from a group home at age twelve, Evan Smoak was raised and trained as an off-the-books government assassin: Orphan X. After he broke with the Orphan Program, Evan disappeared and reinvented himself as the Nowhere Man, a man spoken about only in whispers and dedicated to helping the truly desperate. But this time, the voice on the other end is Jack Johns, the man who raised and trained him, the only father Evan has ever known. Secret government forces are busy trying to scrub the remaining assets and traces of the Orphan Program and they have finally tracked down Jack. With little time remaining, Jack gives Evan his last assignment: find and protect his last protégé and recruit for the program. But Evan isn’t the only one after this last Orphan—the new head of the Orphan Program, Van Sciver, is mustering all the assets at his disposal to take out both Evan (Orphan X) and the target he is trying to protect.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>14</DOCNO>
		<Title>BiIs It Wrong to Try to Pick Up Girls in a Dungeon?, Vol. 6 (light novel) </Title>
		<Author>Fujino Omori </Author>
		<Cover>cover_14</Cover>
		<Text>
			"Hestia, I challenge you to a War Game!" "What's with you, Apollo?" A War Game--an all-out proxy war between gods, and the winner takes all. But what is it that Apollo wants? Hestia's beloved Bell Cranell, of course! With a week to go until the Game, things are bleak enough, but then Lilly is kidnapped by the Soma Familia. The outlook isn't good , but Bell has made many friends through his adventures, and they won't stand idly by. The familia myth continues!
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>15</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Seven or Eight Deaths of Stella Fortuna</Title>
		<Author>Juliet Grames</Author>
		<Cover>cover_15</Cover>
		<Text>
			For Stella Fortuna, death has always been a part of life. Stella’s childhood is full of strange, life-threatening incidents—moments where ordinary situations like cooking eggplant or feeding the pigs inexplicably take lethal turns. Even Stella’s own mother is convinced that her daughter is cursed or haunted. In her rugged Italian village, Stella is considered an oddity—beautiful and smart, insolent and cold. Stella uses her peculiar toughness to protect her slower, plainer baby sister Tina from life’s harshest realities. But she also provokes the ire of her father Antonio: a man who demands subservience from women and whose greatest gift to his family is his absence. When the Fortunas emigrate to America on the cusp of World War II, Stella and Tina must come of age side-by-side in a hostile new world with strict expectations for each of them. Soon Stella learns that her survival is worthless without the one thing her family will deny her at any cost: her independence. In present-day Connecticut, one family member tells this heartrending story, determined to understand the persisting rift between the now-elderly Stella and Tina. A richly told debut, The Seven or Eight Deaths of Stella Fortuna is a tale of family transgressions as ancient and twisted as the olive branch that could heal them.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>16</DOCNO>
		<Title>So I'm a Spider, So What?, Vol. 1 (light novel) (So I'm a Spider, So What? (light novel))</Title>
		<Author>Okina Baba</Author>
		<Cover>cover_16</Cover>
		<Text>
			I used to be a normal high school girl but in the blink of an eye, I woke up in a place I've never seen before and-and I was reborn as a spider?! How could something that's nothing more than a tiny spider (that's me) possibly survive in literally the worst dungeon ever? Are there no rules? There should be some rules! Who the hell is responsible for this? SHOW YOUR FACE!
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>17</DOCNO>
		<Title>That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime, Vol. 1 (That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime</Title>
		<Author>Fuse</Author>
		<Cover>cover_17</Cover>
		<Text>
			Living alone and never having had a girlfriend, 37-year-old Satoru Mikami is dissatisfied with how his life has turned out. But after dying at the hands of a robber, he awakens to a fresh start in a new world...as a slime monster.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>18</DOCNO>
		<Title>Go: A Coming of Age</Title>
		<Author>Kazuki Kaneshiro</Author>
		<Cover>cover_18</Cover>
		<Text>
			As a Korean student in a Japanese high school, Sugihara has had to defend himself against all kinds of bullies. But nothing could have prepared him for the heartache he feels when he falls hopelessly in love with a Japanese girl named Sakurai. Immersed in their shared love for classical music and foreign movies, the two gradually grow closer and closer. One night, after being hit by personal tragedy, Sugihara reveals to Sakurai that he is not Japanese—as his name might indicate. Torn between a chance at self-discovery that he’s ready to seize and the prejudices of others that he can’t control, Sugihara must decide who he wants to be and where he wants to go next. Will Sakurai be able to confront her own bias and accompany him on his journey?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>19</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Wolf and the Watchman: A Novel</Title>
		<Author>Niklas Natt och Dag</Author>
		<Cover>cover_19</Cover>
		<Text>
			One morning in the autumn of 1793, watchman Mikel Cardell is awakened from his drunken slumber with reports of a body seen floating in the Larder, once a pristine lake on Stockholm’s Southern Isle, now a rancid bog. Efforts to identify the bizarrely mutilated corpse are entrusted to incorruptible lawyer Cecil Winge, who enlists Cardell’s help to solve the case. But time is short: Winge’s health is failing, the monarchy is in shambles, and whispered conspiracies and paranoia abound. Winge and Cardell become immersed in a brutal world of guttersnipes and thieves, mercenaries and madams. From a farmer’s son who is led down a treacherous path when he seeks his fortune in the capital to an orphan girl consigned to the workhouse by a pitiless parish priest, their gruesome investigation peels back layer upon layer of the city’s labyrinthine society. The rich and the poor, the pious and the fallen, the living and the dead—all collide and interconnect with the body pulled from the lake. Breathtakingly bold and intricately constructed, The Wolf and the Watchman brings to life the crowded streets, gilded palaces, and dark corners of late-eighteenth-century Stockholm, offering a startling vision of the crimes we commit in the name of justice, and the sacrifices we make in order to survive.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>20</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Saga of Tanya the Evil, Vol. 5 (light novel): Abyssus Abyssum Invocat</Title>
		<Author>Carlo Zen</Author>
		<Cover>cover_20</Cover>
		<Text>
			Barely two months remain until winter, and opinion is split over whether the Empire should launch a full-scale offensive or rest until spring. Time is running out, and the General Staff can't make up their minds. While everyone else is frozen with inaction, the Salamander Kampfgruppe under Tanya's command is singled out for a mission that will ultimately decide the army's course. As they face attacks from a seemingly relentless enemy that leave them without even time to sleep, will Tanya's troops be able to hold out?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>21</DOCNO>
		<Title>Baccano!, Vol. 10 (light novel): 1934 Peter Pan in Chains: Finale</Title>
		<Author>Ryohgo Narita, Katsumi Enami</Author>
		<Cover>cover_21</Cover>
		<Text>
			THE YEAR 1934. In the depths of Alcatraz, Firo, Ladd, Leeza, and the others involved in the underground brawl attempt to figure out their next moves. Meanwhile, in Chicago, as Isaac and Miria try to find each other, the aftermath of what happened at the Russo mansion is affecting the entire city. As the connections between the two locations become clear, the chaos comes to a head in this explosive and heartfelt conclusion to the commotion of 1934!
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>22</DOCNO>
		<Title>Outlining Your Novel: Map Your Way to Success</Title>
		<Author>K. M. Weiland</Author>
		<Cover>cover_22</Cover>
		<Text>
			Can Outlining Help You Write a Better Story?Writers often look upon outlines with fear and trembling. But when properly understood and correctly wielded, the outline is one of the most powerful weapons in a writer’s arsenal.Outlining Your Novel: Map Your Way to Success will:•Help you choose the right type of outline for you•Guide you in brainstorming plot ideas•Aid you in discovering your characters•Show you how to structure your scenes•Explain how to format your finished outline•Instruct you in how to use your outline•Reveal the benefits•Dispel the misconceptionsIncludes exclusive interviews with ten respected authors, answering important questions about outlining.Outlining can organize your writing and help you take your stories to the next level. Find out how!
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>23</DOCNO>
		<Title>Division Maneuver Vol. 1 - A Hero Reincarnated (Light Novel) (Division Maneuver (Light Novel))</Title>
		<Author>Shippo Senoo</Author>
		<Cover>cover_23</Cover>
		<Text>
			When the monstrous Jave attacked, mankind’s strongest warrior died defending humanity--and was reincarnated as a baby. Now, thirteen years later, the Jave have returned! Enrolling in an academy that trains people to use the magic-powered battlesuits known as Division Maneuver, Okegawa Kuon can only operate Division 1, the weakest--until the opportunity to pilot a special, one-of-a-kind suit appears, one that can be activated even with rock-bottom levels of magical power!
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>24</DOCNO>
		<Title>New York: The Novel</Title>
		<Author>Edward Rutherfurd</Author>
		<Cover>cover_24</Cover>
		<Text>
			Edward Rutherfurd celebrates America’s greatest city in a rich, engrossing saga, weaving together tales of families rich and poor, native-born and immigrant—a cast of fictional and true characters whose fates rise and fall and rise again with the city’s fortunes. From this intimate perspective we see New York’s humble beginnings as a tiny Indian fishing village, the arrival of Dutch and British merchants, the Revolutionary War, the emergence of the city as a great trading and financial center, the convulsions of the Civil War, the excesses of the Gilded Age, the explosion of immigration in the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries, the trials of World War II, the near demise of New York in the 1970s and its roaring rebirth in the 1990s, and the attack on the World Trade Center. A stirring mix of battle, romance, family struggles, and personal triumphs, New York: The Novel gloriously captures the search for freedom and opportunity at the heart of our nation’s history.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>25</DOCNO>
		<Title>Percy Jackson and the Olympians The Last Olympian: The Graphic Novel (Percy Jackson and the Olympians)</Title>
		<Author> Rick Riordan</Author>
		<Cover>cover_25</Cover>
		<Text>
			All year the half-bloods have been preparing for battle against the Titans, knowing the odds of victory are grim. Krono's army is stronger than ever, and with every god and half-blood he recruits, the evil Titan's power only grows. While the Olympians struggle to contain the rampaging monster Typhon, Kronos begins his advance on New York City, where Mount Olympus stands virtually unguarded. Now it's up to Percy Jackson and an army of young demigods to stop the Lord of Time. In this epic finale to the New York Times best-selling Percy Jackson and the Olympians series, the long-awaited prophecy surrounding Percy's sixteenth birthday unfolds. As the battle for Western civilization rages on the streets of Manhattan, Percy faces a terrifying suspicion that he may be fighting against his own fate. Relive the showdown in this all new graphic novel adaptation.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>26</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Iliad</Title>
		<Author>Gareth Hinds</Author>
		<Cover>cover_26</Cover>
		<Text>
			More than three thousand years ago, two armies faced each other in an epic battle that rewrote history and came to be known as the Trojan War. The Iliad, Homer's legendary account of this nine-year ordeal, is considered the greatest war story of all time and one of the most important works of Western literature. In this stunning graphic novel adaptation — a thoroughly researched and artfully rendered masterwork — renowned illustrator Gareth Hinds captures all the grim glory of Homer's epic. Dynamic illustrations take readers directly to the plains of Troy, into the battle itself, and lay bare the complex emotions of the men, women, and gods whose struggles fueled the war and determined its outcome. This companion volume to Hinds’s award-winning adaptation of The Odyssey features notes, maps, a cast of characters, and other tools to help readers understand all the action and drama of Homer's epic.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>27</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Serpent's Shadow: The Graphic Novel (The Kane Chronicles)</Title>
		<Author>Rick Riordan</Author>
		<Cover>cover_27</Cover>
		<Text>
			He's b-a-a-ack! Despite their best efforts, Carter and Sadie Kane can't seem to keep Apophis, the chaos snake, down. Now Apophis is threatening to plunge the world into eternal darkness, and the Kanes are faced with the impossible task of having to destroy him once and for all. Unfortunately, the magicians of the House of Life are on the brink of civil war, the gods are divided, and the young initiates of Brooklyn House stand almost alone against the forces of chaos. The Kanes' only hope is an ancient spell that might turn the serpent's own shadow into a weapon, but the magic has been lost for a millennia. To find the answer they need, the Kanes must rely on the murderous ghost of a powerful magician who might be able to lead them to the serpent's shadow . . . or might lead them to their deaths in the depths of the underworld. Nothing less than the mortal world is at stake when the Kane family fulfills its destiny in this thrilling conclusion to the Kane Chronicles. This non-stop thrill ride is adapted and brought to life by Orpheus Collar, who developed the other Kane Chronicles graphic novels and worked on The Lightning Thief; The Graphic Novel; The Lost Hero, The Graphic Novel; and many other titles including The Amazing Spider-Man and Ultimate X-Men.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>28</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Witch Elm: A Novel</Title>
		<Author>Tana French</Author>
		<Cover>cover_28</Cover>
		<Text>
			From the writer who "inspires cultic devotion in readers" (The New Yorker) and has been called "incandescent" by Stephen King, "absolutely mesmerizing" by Gillian Flynn, and "unputdownable" (People), comes a gripping new novel that turns a crime story inside out. Toby is a happy-go-lucky charmer who's dodged a scrape at work and is celebrating with friends when the night takes a turn that will change his life - he surprises two burglars who beat him and leave him for dead. Struggling to recover from his injuries, beginning to understand that he might never be the same man again, he takes refuge at his family's ancestral home to care for his dying uncle Hugo. Then a skull is found in the trunk of an elm tree in the garden - and as detectives close in, Toby is forced to face the possibility that his past may not be what he has always believed. A spellbinding standalone from one of the best suspense writers working today, The Witch Elm asks what we become, and what we're capable of, when we no longer know who we are.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>29</DOCNO>
		<Title>Goblin Slayer, Vol. 7 (light novel) (Goblin Slayer (Light Novel))</Title>
		<Author>Kumo Kagyu</Author>
		<Cover>cover_29</Cover>
		<Text>
			He does not let anyone roll the dice. After High Elf Archer receives notice of a wedding back in her home village, the party sets out for the forest of the elves - and joining them on their trip are Cow Girl and Guild Girl! Goblin Slayer and crew are long overdue for a vacation, and what better place is there to get some rest and relaxation than under the brilliant forest canopy? But things take an unexpected turn when they head upriver for the elf homeland only to see the shadows of goblins looming... And what's more, there's talk of an ancient beast slumbering within the forest. With all this danger close at hand, will there even be a wedding for our heroes to celebrate?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>30</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Huntress: A Novel</Title>
		<Author>Kate Quinn</Author>
		<Cover>cover_30</Cover>
		<Text>
			Bold and fearless, Nina Markova always dreamed of flying. When the Nazis attack the Soviet Union, she risks everything to join the legendary Night Witches, an all-female night bomber regiment wreaking havoc on the invading Germans. When she is stranded behind enemy lines, Nina becomes the prey of a lethal Nazi murderess known as the Huntress, and only Nina's bravery and cunning will keep her alive. Transformed by the horrors he witnessed from Omaha Beach to the Nuremberg Trials, British war correspondent Ian Graham has become a Nazi hunter. Yet one target eludes him: a vicious predator known as the Huntress. To find her, the fierce, disciplined investigator joins forces with the only witness to escape the Huntress alive: the brazen, cocksure Nina. But a shared secret could derail their mission unless Ian and Nina force themselves to confront it. Growing up in post-war Boston, 17-year-old Jordan McBride is determined to become a photographer. When her long-widowed father unexpectedly comes home with a new fiancée, Jordan is thrilled. But there is something disconcerting about the soft-spoken German widow. Certain that danger is lurking, Jordan begins to delve into her new stepmother's past - only to discover that there are mysteries buried deep in her family...secrets that may threaten all Jordan holds dear. In this immersive, heart-wrenching story, Kate Quinn illuminates the consequences of war on individual lives, and the price we pay to seek justice and truth.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>31</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Scam: A Fox and O'Hare Novel</Title>
		<Author>Janet Evanovich</Author>
		<Cover>cover_31</Cover>
		<Text>
			Nicolas Fox is a charming con man and master thief on the run. Kate O’Hare is the FBI agent who is hot on his trail. At least that’s what everyone thinks. In reality, Fox and O’Hare are secretly working together to bring down super-criminals the law can’t touch. Criminals like brutal casino magnate Evan Trace. Evan Trace is running a money-laundering operation through his casino in Macau. Some of his best customers are mobsters, dictators, and global terrorists. Nick and Kate will have to go deep undercover as high-stakes gamblers, wagering millions of dollars—and their lives—in an attempt to topple Trace’s empire. It’s a scam that will take Fox and O’Hare from the Las Vegas strip, to the sun-soaked beaches of Oahu’s North Shore, and into the dark back alleys of Macau. Their only backup—a self-absorbed actor, a Somali pirate, and Kate’s father, an ex-soldier who believes a rocket launcher is the best way to solve every problem. What could possibly go wrong?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>32</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Little Old Lady Who Broke All the Rules: A Novel (League of Pensioners)</Title>
		<Author>Catharina Ingelman-Sundberg</Author>
		<Cover>cover_32</Cover>
		<Text>
			The Best Exotic Marigold Hotel meets The Italian Job in internationally-bestselling author Catharina Ingelman-Sundberg’s witty and insightful comedy of errors about a group of delinquent seniors whose desire for a better quality of life leads them to rob and ransom priceless artwork. Martha Andersson may be seventy-nine-years-old and live in a retirement home, but that doesn’t mean she’s ready to stop enjoying life. So when the new management of Diamond House starts cutting corners to save money, Martha and her four closest friends—Brains, The Rake, Christina and Anna-Gretta (a.k.a. The League of Pensioners)—won’t stand for it. Fed up with early bedtimes and overcooked veggies, this group of feisty seniors sets about to regain their independence, improve their lot, and stand up for seniors everywhere. Their solution? White collar crime. What begins as a relatively straightforward robbery of a nearby luxury hotel quickly escalates into an unsolvable heist at the National Museum. With police baffled and the Mafia hot on their trail, the League of Pensioners has to stay one walker’s length ahead if it’s going to succeed. Told with all the insight and humor of A Man Called Ove or Where’d You Go Bernadette?, The Little Old Lady Who Broke All the Rules is a delightful and heartwarming novel that goes to prove the adage that it’s not the years in your life that count, it’s the life in your years.  
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>33</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Moroccan Girl: A Novel</Title>
		<Author>Charles Cumming</Author>
		<Cover>cover_33</Cover>
		<Text>
			Renowned author Kit Carradine is approached by an MI6 officer with a seemingly straightforward assignment: to track down a mysterious woman hiding somewhere in the exotic, perilous city of Marrakesh. But when Carradine learns the woman is a dangerous fugitive with ties to international terrorism, the glamour of being a spy is soon tainted by fear and betrayal. Lara Bartok is a leading figure in Resurrection, a violent revolutionary movement whose brutal attacks on prominent right-wing public figures have spread hatred and violence across the world. Her disappearance ignites a race between warring intelligence services desperate to find her—at any cost. But as Carradine edges closer to the truth, he finds himself drawn to this brilliant, beautiful, and profoundly complex woman. Caught between increasingly dangerous forces who want Bartok dead, Carradine soon faces an awful choice: to abandon Lara to her fate, or to risk everything trying to save her.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>34</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Music Shop: A Novel</Title>
		<Author>Rachel Joyce</Author>
		<Cover>cover_34</Cover>		
		<Text>
			It is 1988. On a dead-end street in a run-down suburb there is a music shop that stands small and brightly lit, jam-packed with records of every kind. Like a beacon, the shop attracts the lonely, the sleepless, and the adrift; Frank, the shop’s owner, has a way of connecting his customers with just the piece of music they need. Then, one day, into his shop comes a beautiful young woman, Ilse Brauchmann, who asks Frank to teach her about music. Terrified of real closeness, Frank feels compelled to turn and run, yet he is drawn to this strangely still, mysterious woman with eyes as black as vinyl. But Ilse is not what she seems, and Frank has old wounds that threaten to reopen, as well as a past it seems he will never leave behind. Can a man who is so in tune with other people’s needs be so incapable of connecting with the one person who might save him? The journey that these two quirky, wonderful characters make in order to overcome their emotional baggage speaks to the healing power of music—and love—in this poignant, ultimately joyful work of fiction.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>35</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Big Book of Graphic Novels for Minecrafters: Three Unofficial Adventures</Title>
		<Author>Megan Miller</Author>
		<Cover>cover_35</Cover>
		<Text>
			Phoenix, a young miner girl, has never known her parents. She has always dreamed of something greater, of seeing the world outside her village and the magical forest that lies just beyond the walls. One day she takes the risk—just a quick hop over the walls—but her forbidden trip changes the course of her life. Thrust into a world of zombies, creepers, witches, and magical monks, Phoenix finds the adventure she craved, but will she find the bravery she needs to save not only her village but the entire Overworld? Containing The Quest for the Golden Apple, Revenge of the Zombie Monks, and The Ender Eye Prophecy, The Big Book of Graphic Novels for Minecrafters will enchant readers of all ages who love playing Minecraft and love stories full of action, adventure, and bravery.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>36</DOCNO>
		<Title>A Game of Thrones: The Graphic Novels Volumes 1-4</Title>
		<Author>Tommy Patterson George R. R. Martin</Author>
		<Cover>cover_36</Cover>
		<Text>
			George R. R. Martin's epic fantasy masterwork A Game of Thrones is brought to life in the pages of these full-colour graphic novels. This set contains volumes 1 to 4 of a series that is sure to be one of the most coveted collaborations of the year. Winter is coming. Such is the stern motto of House Stark, the northernmost of the fiefdoms that owe allegiance to King Robert Baratheon in far-off King's Landing. There Eddard Stark of Winterfell rules in Robert's name. There his family dwells in peace and comfort: his proud wife, Catelyn; his sons Robb, Brandon, and Rickon; his daughters Sansa and Arya; and his bastard son, Jon Snow. Far to the north, behind the towering Wall, lie savage Wildings and worse - unnatural things relegated to myth during the centuries-long summer, but proving all too real and all too deadly in the turning of the season. Yet a more immediate threat lurks to the south, where Jon Arryn, the Hand of the King, has died under mysterious circumstances.Now Robert is riding north to Winterfell, bringing his queen, the lovely but cold Cersei, his son, the cruel, vainglorious Prince Joffrey, and the queen's brothers Jamie and Tyrion of the powerful and wealthy House Lannister - the first a swordsman without equal, the second a dwarf whose stunted stature belies a brilliant mind. All are heading for Winterfell and a fateful encounter that will change the course of kingdoms. Meanwhile, across the Narrow Sea, Prince Viserys, heir of the fallen House Targaryen, which once ruled all of Westeros, schemes to reclaim the throne with an army of barbarian Dothraki-whose loyalty he will purchase in the only coin left to him: his beautiful yet innocent sister, Daenerys.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>37</DOCNO>
		<Title>CivilWarLand in Bad Decline: Stories and a Novella</Title>
		<Author>George Saunders</Author>
		<Cover>cover_37</Cover>
		<Text>
			Since its publication in 1996, George Saunders’s debut collection has grown in esteem from a cherished cult classic to a masterpiece of the form, inspiring an entire generation of writers along the way. In six stories and a novella, Saunders hatches an unforgettable cast of characters, each struggling to survive in an increasingly haywire world. With a new introduction by Joshua Ferris and a new author’s note by Saunders himself, this edition is essential reading for those seeking to discover or revisit a virtuosic, disturbingly prescient voice.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>38</DOCNO>
		<Title>Father Sergius</Title>
		<Author>Leo Tolstoy</Author>
		<Cover>cover_38</Cover>
		<Text>
			Prince Stepan Kasatsky experiences a disappointment with his fiancé and decides to become a monk! There is a story line, but beneath it, Father Sergius struggles to find peace and, if not happiness, then at least contentment. But he is always disillusioned and ultimately unsatisfied. Only in the end does he find his way by letting go of what he struggled to attain all his life, i.e. to be better than everyone else in whatever he did, and settle for the mundane.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>39</DOCNO>
		<Title>Z: A Novel of Zelda Fitzgerald</Title>
		<Author>Therese Anne Fowler</Author>
		<Cover>cover_39</Cover>
		<Text>
			I wish I could tell everyone who thinks we're ruined, Look closer…and you'll see something extraordinary, mystifying, something real and true. We have never been what we seemed. When beautiful, reckless Southern belle Zelda Sayre meets F. Scott Fitzgerald at a country club dance in 1918, she is seventeen years old and he is a young army lieutenant stationed in Alabama. Before long, the "ungettable" Zelda has fallen for him despite his unsuitability: Scott isn't wealthy or prominent or even a Southerner, and keeps insisting, absurdly, that his writing will bring him both fortune and fame. Her father is deeply unimpressed. But after Scott sells his first novel, This Side of Paradise, to Scribner's, Zelda optimistically boards a train north, to marry him in the vestry of St. Patrick's Cathedral and take the rest as it comes. What comes, here at the dawn of the Jazz Age, is unimagined attention and success and celebrity that will make Scott and Zelda legends in their own time. Everyone wants to meet the dashing young author of the scandalous novel—and his witty, perhaps even more scandalous wife. Zelda bobs her hair, adopts daring new fashions, and revels in this wild new world. Each place they go becomes a playground: New York City, Long Island, Hollywood, Paris, and the French Riviera—where they join the endless party of the glamorous, sometimes doomed Lost Generation that includes Ernest Hemingway, Sara and Gerald Murphy, and Gertrude Stein.Everything seems new and possible. Troubles, at first, seem to fade like morning mist. But not even Jay Gatsby's parties go on forever. Who is Zelda, other than the wife of a famous—sometimes infamous—husband? How can she forge her own identity while fighting her demons and Scott's, too? With brilliant insight and imagination, Therese Anne Fowler's New York Times bestseller brings us Zelda's irresistible story as she herself might have told it.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>40</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Mortal Instruments: The Graphic Novel, Vol. 1</Title>
		<Author>Cassandra Clare</Author>
		<Cover>cover_40</Cover>
		<Text>
			Cassandra Clare's bestselling series, The Mortal Instruments, is adapted into a graphic novel series!
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>41</DOCNO>
		<Title>My Youth Romantic Comedy Is Wrong, As I Expected, Vol. 3 - light novel</Title>
		<Author>Wataru Watari</Author>
		<Cover>cover_41</Cover>
		<Text>
			Nothing ever changes. No friends, no girlfriends--nothing but a solitary life at school... So why is Hachiman so uncomfortable? Maybe it's the fact that their club room is one girl short. There's no way Yukino and Hachiman can solve the problems born from this chain of misunderstandings. The bittersweet time with Totsuka, preparing for battle with Zaimokuza, a secret side of Ms. Hiratsuka...and strip poker? Surrounded by characters sprinting headlong in the wrong direction, will the club ever return to normal?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>42</DOCNO>
		<Title>That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime, Vol. 3 (light novel) (That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime (light novel))</Title>
		<Author>Fuse</Author>
		<Cover>cover_42</Cover>
		<Text>
			After a furious battle with the orcs, peace has once again returned to the Forest of Jura. Rimuru may be heading up the Great Forest of Jura Alliance, but he's mostly worried about finishing his town...until a visit from King Gazel Dwargo of the dwarves turns everything upside down. Not only that, but he's about to have a run-in with an exceptionally dangerous demon lord. What's a slime to do?! 
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>43</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Saga of Tanya the Evil, Vol. 5 (light novel): Abyssus Abyssum Invocat</Title>
		<Author>Carlo Zen</Author>
		<Cover>cover_43</Cover>
		<Text>
			Barely two months remain until winter, and opinion is split over whether the Empire should launch a full-scale offensive or rest until spring. Time is running out, and the General Staff can't make up their minds. While everyone else is frozen with inaction, the Salamander Kampfgruppe under Tanya's command is singled out for a mission that will ultimately decide the army's course. As they face attacks from a seemingly relentless enemy that leave them without even time to sleep, will Tanya's troops be able to hold out?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>44</DOCNO>
		<Title>It Ends with Us: A Novel</Title>
		<Author>Colleen Hoover</Author>
		<Cover>cover_44</Cover>
		<Text>
			Lily hasn't always had it easy, but that's never stopped her from working hard for the life she wants. She's come a long way from the small town in Maine where she grew up - she graduated from college, moved to Boston, and started her own business. So when she feels a spark with a gorgeous neurosurgeon named Ryle Kincaid, everything in Lily's life suddenly seems almost too good to be true. Ryle is assertive, stubborn, and maybe even a little arrogant. He's also sensitive, brilliant, and has a total soft spot for Lily, but Ryle's complete aversion to relationships is disturbing. As questions about her new relationship overwhelm her, so do thoughts of Atlas Corrigan - her first love and a link to the past she left behind. He was her kindred spirit, her protector. When Atlas suddenly reappears, everything Lily has built with Ryle is threatened. With this bold and deeply personal novel, Colleen Hoover delivers a heart-wrenching story that breaks exciting new ground for her as a writer. It Ends With Us is an unforgettable tale of love that comes at the ultimate price.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>45</DOCNO>
		<Title>Monster: A Graphic Novel</Title>
		<Author>Walter Dean Myers</Author>
		<Cover>cover_45</Cover>
		<Text>
			Monster is a multi-award-winning, provocative coming-of-age story about Steve Harmon, a teenager awaiting trial for a murder and robbery. As Steve acclimates to juvenile detention and goes to trial, he envisions how his ordeal would play out on the big screen. Monster was the first-ever Michael L. Printz Award recipient, an ALA Best Book, a Coretta Scott King Honor selection, and a National Book Award finalist. Now Monster has been adapted into a graphic novel by Guy Sims, with stunning black-and-white art from Dawud Anyabwile, Guy's brother. Fans of Monster and of the work of Walter Dean Myers—and even kids who think they don't like to read—will devour this graphic adaptation.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>46</DOCNO>
		<Title>Claudia and Mean Janine (The Baby-Sitters Club Graphic Novel #4): A Graphix Book</Title>
		<Author>Raina Telgemeier</Author>
		<Cover>cover_46</Cover>
		<Text>
			Claudia and her sister, Janine, may as well be from two different planets. Claudia, who pays more attention to her artwork and The Baby-sitters Club than her homework, feels like she can't compete with her perfect sister. Janine studies nonstop, gets straight As, and even takes college-level courses! But when something unexpected happens to the most beloved person in their family, will the sisters be able to put aside their differences? Raina Telgemeier, using the signature style featured in her acclaimed graphic novels Smile and Sisters, perfectly captures all the drama and charm of the original novel!
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>47</DOCNO>
		<Title>Tell No One: A Novel</Title>
		<Author>Harlan Coben</Author>
		<Cover>cover_47</Cover>
		<Text>
			For Dr. David Beck, the loss was shattering. And every day for the past eight years, he has relived the horror of what happened. The gleaming lake. The pale moonlight. The piercing screams. The night his wife was taken. The last night he saw her alive. Everyone tells him it's time to move on, to forget the past once and for all. But for David Beck, there can be no closure. A message has appeared on his computer, a phrase only he and his dead wife know. Suddenly Beck is taunted with the impossible—that somewhere, somehow, Elizabeth is alive. Beck has been warned to tell no one. And he doesn't. Instead, he runs from the people he trusts the most, plunging headlong into a search for the shadowy figure whose messages hold out a desperate hope. But already Beck is being hunted down. He's headed straight into the heart of a dark and deadly secret—and someone intends to stop him before he gets there.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>48</DOCNO>
		<Title>Reincarnated as a Sword (Light Novel) Vol. 2</Title>
		<Author>Yuu Tanaka</Author>
		<Cover>cover_48</Cover>
		<Text>
			People remain skeptical of Fran’s abilities despite her achievements with Teacher, and so, accused of playing favorites, the Guild Master assigns the duo a difficult mission to prove their worth. Fran and Teacher don’t much care what anyone thinks of them, but once they venture into the snare-filled Spider's Lair, even they realize they may have bitten off more than they can chew.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>49</DOCNO>
		<Title>Kristy's Big Day (The Baby-Sitters Club Graphix #6): Full-Color Edition</Title>
		<Author>Ann M. Martin</Author>
				<Cover>cover_49</Cover>
		<Text>
			Kristy's mom is getting married, and Kristy is going to be a bridesmaid! The only problem? Fourteen kids are coming to town for the wedding. Kristy, Claudia, Mary Anne, Stacey, Dawn, and Mallory think they can handle it, but that's before they spend a week changing diapers, stopping arguments, solving mix-ups, and planning activities. It's the biggest job the BSC has ever had, but they'll work together to make sure Kristy's big day is a success!
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>50</DOCNO>
		<Title>So I'm a Spider, So What?, Vol. 3 (light novel) (So I'm a Spider, So What? (light novel))</Title>
		<Author>Okina Baba</Author>
		<Cover>cover_50</Cover>
		<Text>
			Who knew being strong meant going hungry...? After making it through the fiery Middle Stratum and evolving again, things have been a cakewalk for me-and also one of the worst times of my life. I've gotten so strong that every living thing is avoiding me like the plague. Even monsters that wouldn't leave me alone for a second are running away like their lives depend on it. I mean...all I want to do is eat them! Is that too much to ask for?! At this point, about the only thing that WON'T flee the moment it sees me is the earth dragon Araba, and I sure as hell can't have that for a meal...right...?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>51</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Inglorious Arts</Title>
		<Author>Alan Haruska </Author>
		<Cover>cover_51</Cover>		
		<Text>
			Seasoned New York lawyer Alec Brno, first introduced in Pardon the Ravens, is tested again by overlapping personal and professional crises. Early on, he’s asked to rescue his firm’s oldest client, who is being sued vindictively by a giant public utility, as well as the firm’s largest client, embroiled in a politically motivated suit before a lunatic federal judge. To avoid crippling results, and the loss of more than 200,000 jobs, Alec must somehow get rid of both cases almost immediately and stop thousands of others from suing.  This seemingly impossible assignment arrives as Alec’s adopted sixteen-year-old daughter, the inheritor of a Mafia fortune, is targeted in a sex-slave scheme by her uncle, the capo famiglia. Distractions only intensify when Alec’s beautiful sister-in-law, who arrives from Dublin, looking and acting so much like his deceased wife, becomes a board piece in the Mob game. The Inglorious Arts follows Alec’s heroics as he deals with corporate intrigues, political maneuvering, two high-s			takes courtroom battles, Mob terror, and the frantic race to save the lives of the women he loves.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>52</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Good Detective</Title>
		<Author>John McMahon</Author>
		<Cover>cover_52</Cover>
		<Text>
			"John McMahon is one of those rare writers who seem to have sprung out of nowhere. His first novel, The Good Detective, which is pretty much perfect, features a decent if flawed hero battling personal troubles while occupied with a murder case of great consequence to his community."--New York Times Book Review. Introducing Detective P.T. Marsh in a swift and bruising debut where Elmore Leonard's staccato prose meets Greg Iles' Southern settings.
			How can you solve a crime if you've killed the prime suspect?Detective P.T. Marsh was a rising star on the police force of Mason Falls, Georgia--until his wife and young son died in an accident. Since that night, he's lost the ability to see the line between smart moves and disastrous decisions. Such as when he agrees to help out a woman by confronting her abusive boyfriend. When the next morning he gets called to the scene of his newest murder case, he is stunned to arrive at the house of the very man he beat up the night before. He could swear the guy was alive when he left, but can he be sure? What's certain is that his fingerprints are all over the crime scene.  The trouble is only beginning. When the dead body of a black teenager is found in a burned-out field with a portion of a blackened rope around his neck, P.T. realizes he might have killed the number-one suspect of this horrific crime. Amid rising racial tension and media scrutiny, P.T. uncovers something sinister at the heart of the boy's murde			r--a conspiracy leading all the way back to the time of the Civil War. Risking everything to unravel the puzzle even as he fights his own personal demons, P.T. races headlong toward an incendiary and life-altering showdown

		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>53</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Border</Title>
		<Author>Don Winslow </Author>
		<Cover>cover_53</Cover>
		<Text>
			ONE OF THE MOST ACCLAIMED BOOKS OF THE YEAR
			"A big, sprawling, ultimately stunning crime tableau." – Janet Maslin, New York Times
			"You can't ask for more emotionally moving entertainment." – Stephen King
			"One of the best thriller writers on the planet." – Esquire
			The explosive, highly anticipated conclusion to the epic Cartel trilogy from the New York Timesbestselling author of The Force
			What do you do when there are no borders? When the lines you thought existed simply vanish?  How do you plant your feet to make a stand when you no longer know what side you’re on?
			The war has come home.
			For over forty years, Art Keller has been on the front lines of America’s longest conflict: The War on Drugs. His obsession to defeat the world’s most powerful, wealthy, and lethal kingpin―the godfather of the Sinaloa Cartel, Adán Barrera―has left him bloody and scarred, cost him the people he loves, even taken a piece of his soul.
			Now Keller is elevated to the highest ranks of the DEA, only to find that in destroying one monster he has created thirty more that are wreaking even more chaos and suffering in his beloved Mexico. But not just there.
			Barrera’s final legacy is the heroin epidemic scourging America. Throwing himself into the gap to stem the deadly flow, Keller finds himself surrounded by enemies―men who want to kill him, politicians who want to destroy him, and worse, the unimaginable―an incoming administration that’s in bed with the very drug traffickers that Keller is trying to bring down.
			Art Keller is at war with not only the cartels, but with his own government. And the long fight has taught him more than he ever imagined. Now, he learns the final lesson―there are no borders.
			In a story that moves from deserts of Mexico to Wall Street, from the slums of Guatemala to the marbled corridors of Washington, D.C., Winslow follows a new generation of narcos, the cops who fight them, street traffickers, addicts, politicians, money-launderers, real-estate moguls, and mere children fleeing the violence for the chance of a life in a new country.
			A shattering tale of vengeance, violence, corruption and justice, this last novel in Don Winslow’s magnificent, award-winning, internationally bestselling trilogy is packed with unforgettable, drawn-from-the-headlines scenes. Shocking in its brutality, raw in its humanity, The Border is an unflinching portrait of modern America, a story of—and for—our time.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>54</DOCNO>
		<Title>A Discovery of Witches: A Novel (All Souls Trilogy, Book 1) </Title>
		<Author>Deborah Harkness</Author>
		<Cover>cover_54</Cover>
		<Text>
			Book one of the New York Times-bestselling All Souls trilogy—"a wonderfully imaginative grown-up fantasy with all the magic of Harry Potter and Twilight” (People). 
			Now “[a] hot show that’s like Twilight meets Outlander” (Thrillist) airing Sundays on AMC and BBC America, as well as streaming on Sundance Now and Shudder.
			Deborah Harkness’s sparkling debut, A Discovery of Witches, has brought her into the spotlight and galvanized fans around the world. In this tale of passion and obsession, Diana Bishop, a young scholar and a descendant of witches, discovers a long-lost and enchanted alchemical manuscript, Ashmole 782, deep in Oxford's Bodleian Library. Its reappearance summons a fantastical underworld, which she navigates with her leading man, vampire geneticist Matthew Clairmont
			Harkness has created a universe to rival those of Anne Rice, Diana Gabaldon, and Elizabeth Kostova, and she adds a scholar's depth to this riveting tale of magic and suspense. The story continues in book two, Shadow of Night, and concludes with The Book of Life.	
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>55</DOCNO>
		<Title>Shadow of Night: A Novel (All Souls Trilogy, Book 2)</Title>
		<Author>Deborah Harkness</Author>
		<Cover>cover_55</Cover>
		<Text>
			The #1 New York Times–bestselling sequel to A Discovery of Witches, book two of the All Souls Trilogy—“as enchanting, engrossing, and impossible to put down as its predecessor” (Miami Herald).
			Look for the hit TV series “A Discovery of Witches” airing Sundays on AMC and BBC America, and streaming on Sundance Now and Shudder.
			J. K. Rowling, Stephenie Meyer, Anne Rice—only a few writers capture the imagination the way that Deborah Harkness has with her New York Times–bestselling All Souls trilogy. A Discovery of Witches introduces reluctant witch Diana Bishop, vampire geneticist Matthew Clairmont, and the battle for a lost, enchanted manuscript known as Ashmole 782.
			Picking up from A Discovery of Witches’ cliffhanger ending, Shadow of Night takes Diana and Matthew on a trip through time to Elizabethan London, where they are plunged into a world of spies, magic, and a coterie of Matthew’s old friends, the School of Night. As the search for Ashmole 782 deepens and Diana seeks out a witch to tutor her in magic, the net of Matthew’s past tightens around them, and they embark on a very different—and vastly more dangerous—journey.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>56</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Book of Life: A Novel (All Souls Trilogy, Book 3)</Title>
		<Author>Deborah Harkness</Author>
		<Cover>cover_56</Cover>
		<Text>
			The #1 New York Times bestselling series finale and sequel to A Discovery of Witches and Shadow of Night. 
			Look for the hit TV series “A Discovery of Witches” airing Sundays on AMC and BBC America, and streaming on Sundance Now and Shudder.
			After traveling through time in Shadow of Night, the second book in Deborah Harkness’s enchanting series, historian and witch Diana Bishop and vampire scientist Matthew Clairmont return to the present to face new crises and old enemies. At Matthew’s ancestral home at Sept-Tours, they reunite with the cast of characters from A Discovery of Witches—with one significant exception. But the real threat to their future has yet to be revealed, and when it is, the search for Ashmole 782 and its missing pages takes on even more urgency. In the trilogy’s final volume, Harkness deepens her themes of power and passion, family and caring, past deeds and their present consequences. In ancestral homes and university laboratories, using ancient knowledge and modern science, from the hills of the Auvergne to the palaces of Venice and beyond, the couple at last learn what the witches discovered so many centuries ago.
			With more than one million copies sold in the United States and appearing in thirty-eight foreign editions, A Discovery of Witches and Shadow of Night have landed on all of the major bestseller lists and garnered rave reviews from countless publications. Eagerly awaited by Harkness’s legion of fans, The Book of Life brings this superbly written series to a deeply satisfying close.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>57</DOCNO>
		<Title>Metropolis</Title>
		<Author>Philip Kerr</Author>
		<Cover>cover_57</Cover>
		<Text>
			"[Metropolis is] a perfect goodbye--and first hello--to its hero...Bernie Gunther has, at last, come home."--Washington Post
			New York Times-bestselling author Philip Kerr treats readers to his beloved hero's origins, exploring Bernie Gunther's first weeks on Berlin's Murder Squad.
			Summer, 1928. Berlin, a city where nothing is verboten. 
			In the night streets, political gangs wander, looking for fights. Daylight reveals a beleaguered populace barely recovering from the postwar inflation, often jobless, reeling from the reparations imposed by the victors. At central police HQ, the Murder Commission has its hands full. A killer is on the loose and though he scatters many clues, each is a dead end. It's almost as if he is taunting the cops. Meanwhile, the press is having a field day. 
			This is what Bernie Gunther finds on his first day with the Murder Commisson. He's been taken on beacuse the people at the top have noticed him--they think he has the makings of a first-rate detective. But not just yet. Right now, he has to listen and learn. 
			Metropolis, completed just before Philip Kerr's untimely death, is the capstone of a fourteen-book journey through the life of Kerr's signature character, Bernhard Genther, a sardonic and wisecracking homicide detective caught up in an increasingly Nazified Berlin police department. In many ways, it is Bernie's origin story and, as Kerr's last novel, it is also, alas, his end. 
			Metropolis is also a tour of a city in chaos: of its seedy sideshows and sex clubs, of the underground gangs that run its rackets, and its bewildered citizens--the lost, the homeless, the abandoned. It is Berlin as it edges toward the new world order that Hitler will soo usher in. And Bernie? He's a quick study and he's learning a lot. Including, to his chagrin, that when push comes to shove, he isn't much better than the gangsters in doing whatever her must to get what he wants.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>58</DOCNO>
		<Title>Greeks Bearing Gifts</Title>
		<Author>Philip Kerr</Author>
		<Cover>cover_58</Cover>
		<Text>
			An NPR Book of the Year
			A Crime Reads Best Crime Book of 2018. A vicious murder puts Bernie Gunther on the trail of World War 2 criminals in Greece in this riveting historical thriller in Philip Kerr's New York Times bestselling series.
			Munich, 1956. Bernie Gunther has a new name, a chip on his shoulder, and a dead-end career when an old friend arrives to repay a debt and encourages "Christoph Ganz" to take a job as a claims adjuster in a major German insurance company with a client in Athens, Greece.
			Under the cover of his new identity, Bernie begins to investigate a claim by Siegfried Witzel, a brutish former Wehrmacht soldier who served in Greece during the war. Witzel's claimed losses are large , and, even worse, they may be the stolen spoils of Greek Jews deported to Auschwitz. But when Bernie tries to confront Witzel, he finds that someone else has gotten to him first, leaving a corpse in his place.
			Enter Lieutenant Leventis, who recognizes in this case the highly grotesque style of a killer he investigated during the height of the war. Back then, a young Leventis suspected an S.S. officer whose connection to the German government made him untouchable. He's kept that man's name in his memory all these years, waiting for his second chance at justice...
			Working together, Leventis and Bernie hope to put their cases--new and old--to bed. But there's a much more sinister truth to acknowledge: A killer has returned to Athens...one who may have never left.
		</Text>
	</DOC>	
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>59</DOCNO>
		<Title>Diary of a Dead Man on Leave</Title>
		<Author>David Downing</Author>
		<Cover>cover_59</Cover>
		<Text>
			From bestselling author David Downing, master of historical espionage, comes a heart-wrenching depiction of Germany in the days leading up to World War II and the difficult choices of one man of conviction. 
			In April 1938, a man calling himself Josef Hofmann arrives at a boarding house in Hamm, Germany, and lets a room from the widow who owns it. Fifty years later, Walter Gersdorff, the widow’s son, who was eleven years old in the spring of 1938, discovers the carefully hidden diary the boarder had kept during his stay, even though he never should have written any of its contents down.
			What Walter finds is a chronicle of one the most tumultuous years in German history, narrated by a secret agent on a deadly mission. Josef Hofmann was not the returned Argentinian immigrant he’d said he was—he was a communist spy under Moscow’s command trying to reconnect with remaining members of Germany’s suppressed communist party. Hofmann’s bosses believe the common workers are the only way to stop the German war machine from within. Posing as a railroad man, Hofmann sets out on his game of “Russian roulette,” approaching Hamm’s ex-party members one at a time and delicately feeling out their allegiances.
			He always knew his mission would most likely end in his death, and he was satisfied to make that sacrifice for the revolution if it could help stop Hitler and his abominable ideology. But as he grows close to the Gersdorffs, accidentally stepping into the role of the father Walter never had, Hofmann begins to wish for another kind of hope in his life.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>60</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Second Sleep</Title>
		<Author>Robert Harris</Author>
		<Cover>cover_60</Cover>
		<Text>
			From the internationally best-selling author of Fatherland and the Cicero Trilogy--a chilling and dark new thriller unlike anything Robert Harris has done before.
			1468. A young priest, Christopher Fairfax, arrives in a remote Exmoor village to conduct the funeral of his predecessor. The land around is strewn with ancient artefacts--coins, fragments of glass, human bones--which the old parson used to collect. Did his obsession with the past lead to his death?
     			Fairfax becomes determined to discover the truth. Over the course of the next six days, everything he believes--about himself, his faith, and the history of his world--will be tested to destruction.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>61</DOCNO>
		<Title>Agent Running in the Field</Title>
		<Author> John Le Carre</Author>
		<Cover>cover_61</Cover>
		<Text>
			A new novel from the #1 New York Times bestselling author John le Carré
			Set in London in 2018, Agent Running in the Field follows a twenty-six year old solitary figure who, in a desperate attempt to resist the political turbulence swirling around him, makes connections that will take him down a dangerous path. In his plot and characterization le Carré is as thrilling as ever and in the way he writes about our times he proves himself, once again, to be the greatest chronicler of our age.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>62</DOCNO>
		<Title>Under Occupation</Title>
		<Author>Alan Furst</Author>
		<Cover>cover_62</Cover>
		<Text>
			From the master of espionage and intrigue, this novel about heroic resistance fighters in 1942 occupied Paris is based on true events of Polish prisoners in Nazi Germany, who smuggled valuable intelligence to Paris and the resistance.
			Occupied Paris in 1942, a dark, treacherous city now ruled by the German security services, where French resistance networks are working secretly to defeat Hitler. Just before he dies, a man being chased by the Gestapo hands off to Paul Ricard a strange looking drawing. It looks like a part for a military weapon; Ricard realizes it must be an important document smuggled out of Germany to aid the resistance. As Ricard is drawn deeper and deeper into the French resistance network, his increasingly dangerous assignments lead him to travel to Germany, and along the underground safe houses of the resistance--and to meet the mysterious and beautiful Leila, a professional spy.
			Alan Furst has been called "one of the best contemporary writers" by David McCullough, and "the most talented espionage novelist of our generation" by Vince Flynn.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>63</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Department of Sensitive Crimes</Title>
		<Author>Alexander McCall Smith</Author>
		<Cover>cover_63</Cover>
		<Text>
			In the Swedish criminal justice system, certain cases are considered especially strange and difficult, in Malmö, the dedicated detectives who investigate these crimes are members of an elite squad known as the Sensitive Crimes Division.These are their stories.
			The first case: the small matter of a man stabbed in the back of the knee. Who would perpetrate such a crime and why? Next: a young woman's imaginary boyfriend goes missing. But how on earth do you search for someone who doesn't exist? And in the final investigation: eerie secrets that are revealed under a full moon may not seem so supernatural in the light of day. No case is too unusual, too complicated, or too, well insignificant for this squad to solve.
			The team: Ulf “the Wolf” Varg, the top dog, thoughtful and diligent; Anna Bengsdotter, who's in love with Varg's car (and possibly Varg too); Carl Holgersson, who likes nothing more than filling out paperwork; and Erik Nykvist, who is deeply committed to fly fishing.
			With the help of a rather verbose local police officer, this crack team gets to the bottom of cases other detectives can't or won't bother to handle. Equal parts hilarious and heartening, The Department of Sensitive Crimes is a tour de farce from a true master.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>64</DOCNO>
		<Title>The American Agent</Title>
		<Author>Jacqueline Winspear</Author>
		<Cover>cover_64</Cover>
		<Text>
			Beloved heroine Maisie Dobbs, “one of the great fictional heroines” (Parade), investigates the mysterious murder of an American war correspondent in London during the Blitz in a page-turning tale of love and war, terror and survival.
			When Catherine Saxon, an American correspondent reporting on the war in Europe, is found murdered in her London digs, news of her death is concealed by British authorities. Serving as a linchpin between Scotland Yard and the Secret Service, Robert MacFarlane pays a visit to Maisie Dobbs, seeking her help. He is accompanied by an agent from the US Department of Justice—Mark Scott, the American who helped Maisie escape Hitler’s Munich in 1938. MacFarlane asks Maisie to work with Scott to uncover the truth about Saxon’s death.
			As the Germans unleash the full terror of their blitzkrieg upon the British Isles, raining death and destruction from the skies, Maisie must balance the demands of solving this dangerous case with her need to protect Anna, the young evacuee she has grown to love and wants to adopt. Entangled in an investigation linked to the power of wartime propaganda and American political intrigue being played out in Britain, Maisie will face losing her dearest friend—and the possibility that she might be falling in love again.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>65</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Fatherland Files (A Gereon Rath Mystery)</Title>
		<Author>Volker Kutscher </Author>
		<Cover>cover_65</Cover>
		<Text>
			July 1932. When a drowned man is found in a freight elevator in Haus Vaterland, the giant pleasure palace on Potsdamer Platz, Inspector Gereon Rath is called in to investigate. It’s not that Rath hasn’t problems enough. His hunt for a mysterious contract killer has been stalled for weeks, and his on-off lover, Charlotte Ritter, has just begun her probationary year with Berlin CID. The corpse in Haus Vaterland looks to be part of a series of murders whose trail leads eastwards to the Polish border - and beyond.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>66</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Dirty Parts of the Bible</Title>
		<Author>Sam Torode</Author>
		<Cover>cover_66</Cover>
		<Text>
			Semifinalist for the Amazon Breakthrough Novel Award and previous #1 Bestseller in Humorous Literary Fiction
			"A rich and soulful novel...steeped in wanderlust and whimsy." --Publishers Weekly
			"The Dirty Parts of the Bible might just be the long-awaited Great American Novel." --New York Times bestselling author John M. Perkins
			The Dirty Parts of the Bible is a humorous adventure across America during the Great Depression--a rollicking tale of love and liquor, preachers and prostitutes, trains and treasure, sure to appeal to fans of O Brother Where Art Thou?, Water for Elephants, Mark Twain, Willie Nelson, and Johnny Cash.
			*    *    *    *
			It's 1936, and Tobias Henry is stuck in the frozen hinterlands of Michigan. Tobias is obsessed with two things: God and girls.
			Mostly girls, of course.
			But being a Baptist preacher's son, he can't escape God.
			When his father is blinded in a bizarre accident (involving hard cider and bird droppings), Tobias must ride the rails to Texas to recover a long-hidden stash of money. Along the way, he's initiated into the hobo brotherhood by Craw, a ribald vagabond-philosopher. Obstacles arise in the form of a saucy prostitute, a flaming boxcar, and a man-eating catfish. But when he meets Sarah, a tough farm girl under a dark curse, he finds out that the greatest challenge of all is love.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>67</DOCNO>
		<Title>On the Island</Title>
		<Author>Tracey Garvis Graves</Author>
		<Cover>cover_67</Cover>
		<Text>
			In this runaway New York Times bestseller, a harrowing near-death experience brings together an English teacher and her student as they struggle to survive on a desert island.
			Sixteen-year-old T.J. Callahan has no desire to go anywhere. With his cancer in remission, all he wants is to get back to his normal life. But his parents insist that he spend the summer catching up on the school he missed while he was sick.
			Anna Emerson is a thirty-year-old English teacher who has been worn down by the cold Chicago winters and a relationship that’s going nowhere. To break up the monotony of everyday life, she jumps at the chance to spend the summer on a tropical island tutoring T.J.
			Anna and T.J. board a private plane headed to the Callahans’ summer home, but as they fly over the Maldives’ twelve hundred islands, the unthinkable happens: their plane crashes in shark-infested waters. They make it to shore, but soon discover they’re stranded on an uninhabited island.
			At first, their only thought is survival. But as the days turn to weeks, and then months, and as birthdays pass, the castaways must brave violent tropical storms, the many dangers lurking in the sea, and the worst threat of all—the possibility that T.J.’s cancer could return. With only each other for love and support, these two lost souls must come to terms with their situation and find compaionship in one another in the moments they need it most.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>68</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Extraordinary Life of Sam Hell</Title>
		<Author>Robert Dugoni</Author>
		<Cover>cover_68</Cover>
		<Text>
			Wall Street Journal and New York Times bestselling author Robert Dugoni’s coming-of-age story is, according to Booklist, “a novel that, if it doesn’t cross entirely over into John Irving territory, certainly nestles in close to the border.”
			Sam Hill always saw the world through different eyes. Born with red pupils, he was called “Devil Boy” or Sam “Hell” by his classmates; “God’s will” is what his mother called his ocular albinism. Her words were of little comfort, but Sam persevered, buoyed by his mother’s devout faith, his father’s practical wisdom, and his two other misfit friends.
			Sam believed it was God who sent Ernie Cantwell, the only African American kid in his class, to be the friend he so desperately needed. And that it was God’s idea for Mickie Kennedy to storm into Our Lady of Mercy like a tornado, uprooting every rule Sam had been taught about boys and girls.
			Forty years later, Sam, a small-town eye doctor, is no longer certain anything was by design—especially not the tragedy that caused him to turn his back on his friends, his hometown, and the life he’d always known. Running from the pain, eyes closed, served little purpose. Now, as he looks back on his life, Sam embarks on a journey that will take him halfway around the world. This time, his eyes are wide open—bringing into clear view what changed him, defined him, and made him so afraid, until he can finally see what truly matters.
			Winner of Suspense Magazine’s Crimson Scribe Award.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>69</DOCNO>
		<Title>True Places</Title>
		<Author>Sonja Yoerg</Author>
		<Cover>cover_69</Cover>
		<Text>
			An Amazon Charts and Washington Post bestseller.
			“True Places is a beautiful reminder that though we may busy ourselves seeking what we want, what we need has an uncanny way of finding us.” —Camille Pagán, bestselling author of Life and Other Near-Death Experiences
			A girl emerges from the woods, starved, ill, and alone…and collapses.
			Suzanne Blakemore hurtles along the Blue Ridge Parkway, away from her overscheduled and completely normal life, and encounters the girl. As Suzanne rushes her to the hospital, she never imagines how the encounter will change her—a change she both fears and desperately needs.
			Suzanne has the perfect house, a successful husband, and a thriving family. But beneath the veneer of an ideal life, her daughter is rebelling, her son is withdrawing, her husband is oblivious to it all, and Suzanne is increasingly unsure of her place in the world. After her discovery of the ethereal sixteen-year-old who has never experienced civilization, Suzanne is compelled to invite Iris into her family’s life and all its apparent privileges.
			But Iris has an independence, a love of solitude, and a discomfort with materialism that contrasts with everything the Blakemores stand for—qualities that awaken in Suzanne first a fascination, then a longing. Now Suzanne can’t help but wonder: Is she destined to save Iris, or is Iris the one who will save her?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>70</DOCNO>
		<Title>My Sister's Grave (Tracy Crosswhite Book 1)</Title>
		<Author>Robert Dugoni</Author>
		<Cover>cover_70</Cover>
		<Text>
			The first book in the series that has garnered millions of readers across the globe, from New York Times bestselling author Robert Dugoni.
			Tracy Crosswhite has spent twenty years questioning the facts surrounding her sister Sarah’s disappearance and the murder trial that followed. She doesn’t believe that Edmund House—a convicted rapist and the man condemned for Sarah’s murder—is the guilty party. Motivated by the opportunity to obtain real justice, Tracy became a homicide detective with the Seattle PD and dedicated her life to tracking down killers.
			When Sarah’s remains are finally discovered near their hometown in the northern Cascade mountains of Washington State, Tracy is determined to get the answers she’s been seeking. As she searches for the real killer, she unearths dark, long-kept secrets that will forever change her relationship to her past—and open the door to deadly danger.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>71</DOCNO>
		<Title>Her Final Breath (Tracy Crosswhite Book 2)</Title>
		<Author>Robert Dugoni </Author>
		<Cover>cover_71</Cover>
		<Text>
			Tracy Crosswhite returns in the second book in the page-turning series by New York Times bestselling author Robert Dugoni.
			Homicide detective Tracy Crosswhite has returned to the police force after the sensational retrial of her sister’s killer. Still scarred from that ordeal, Tracy is pulled into an investigation that threatens to end her career, if not her life.
			A serial killer known as the Cowboy is killing young women in cheap motels in North Seattle. Even after a stalker leaves a menacing message for Crosswhite, suggesting the killer or a copycat could be targeting her personally, she is charged with bringing the murderer to justice. With clues scarce and more victims dying, Tracy realizes the key to solving the murders may lie in a decade-old homicide investigation that others, including her captain, Johnny Nolasco, would prefer to keep buried. With the Cowboy on the hunt, can Tracy find the evidence to stop him, or will she become his next victim?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>72</DOCNO>
		<Title>In the Clearing (Tracy Crosswhite Book 3)</Title>
		<Author>Robert Dugoni</Author>
		<Cover>cover_72</Cover>
		<Text>
			The gripping third book in the internationally acclaimed series by New York Times bestselling author Robert Dugoni.
			Detective Tracy Crosswhite has a skill, and a soft spot, for tackling unsolved crimes. Having lost her own sister to murder at a young age, Tracy has dedicated her career to bringing justice and closure to the families and friends of victims of crime.
			So when Jenny, a former police academy classmate and protégé, asks Tracy to help solve a cold case that involves the suspicious suicide of a Native American high school girl forty years earlier, Tracy agrees. Following up on evidence Jenny’s detective father collected when he was the investigating deputy, Tracy probes one small town’s memory and finds dark, well-concealed secrets hidden within the community’s fabric. Can Tracy uphold the promise she’s made to the dead girl’s family and deliver the truth of what happened to their daughter? Or will she become the next victim?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>73</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Trapped Girl (Tracy Crosswhite Book 4)</Title>
		<Author>Robert Dugoni</Author>
		<Cover>cover_73</Cover>
		<Text>
			In this #1 Wall Street Journal bestseller, Tracy Crosswhite must first identify the victim to catch the killer.
			When a woman’s body is discovered submerged in a crab pot in the chilly waters of Puget Sound, Detective Tracy Crosswhite finds herself with a tough case to untangle. Before they can identify the killer, Tracy and her colleagues on the Seattle PD’s Violent Crimes Section must figure out who the victim is. Her autopsy, however, reveals she may have gone to great lengths to conceal her identity. So who was she running from?
			After evidence surfaces that their Jane Doe may be a woman who suspiciously disappeared months earlier, Tracy is once again haunted by the memory of her sister’s unsolved murder. Dredging up details from the woman’s past leads to conflicting clues that only seem to muddy the investigation. As Tracy begins to uncover a twisted tale of brutal betrayal and desperate greed, she’ll find herself risking everything to confront a killer who won’t go down without a deadly fight. Once again, New York Times bestselling author Robert Dugoni delivers a taut, riveting thriller in the fourth installment of his acclaimed Tracy Crosswhite series.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>74</DOCNO>
		<Title>Easily Amused</Title>
		<Author>Karen McQuestion</Author>
		<Cover>cover_74</Cover>
		<Text>
			Karen McQuestion deftly blends romance and comedy in this delightful romp where love is discovered in the most unexpected of places.
			When twenty-nine-year-old Lola Watson unexpectedly inherits a rambling house in the suburbs, she thinks her life just couldn't be more perfect—until her new neighbors make her their “project,” a heartbroken high school friend crashes indefinitely at her house, and her younger sister announces she's getting married, on Lola's thirtieth birthday. Suddenly Lola's not so keen on her newfound domestic bliss. But when she meets handsome, mysterious Ryan Moriarty, Lola dares to hope she's found the perfect guy to one-up her sister and add a little spice back into her life.
			This lighthearted romantic comedy from Karen McQuestion is headlined by a charming cast of characters, led by the self-deprecatingly funny Lola. Breezy and fun, Easily Amused serves as a gentle, often amusing reminder that love can often be found in the place we least expect—under our very noses.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>75</DOCNO>
		<Title>Half Upon a Time</Title>
		<Author>James Riley</Author>
		<Cover>cover_75</Cover>
		<Text>
			Life’s no fairy tale for Jack. After all, his father's been missing ever since that incident with the beanstalk and the giant, and his grandfather keeps pushing him to get out and find a princess to rescue. Who'd want to rescue a snobby, entitled princess anyway? Especially one that falls out of the sky wearing a shirt that says "Punk Princess," and still denies she's royalty. In fact, May doesn't even believe in magic. Yeah, what's that about? May does need help though--a huntsman is chasing her, her grandmother has been kidnapped, and Jack thinks it’s all because of the Wicked Queen . . . mostly because May’s grandmother might just be the long-lost Snow White. Jack and May's thrillingly hilarious adventure combines all the classic stories—fractured as a broken magic mirror—into one epic novel for the ages.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>76</DOCNO>
		<Title>Under the Mercy Trees</Title>
		<Author>Heather Newton</Author>
		<Cover>cover_76</Cover>
		<Text>
			“[An] eloquent, sorrowful novel....Readers of both Pat Conroy, on one hand, and Carson McCullers, on the other, will relish Newton’s flawed characters and piquant portrayal of small town life.” —Booklist (starred review)
			“Under the Mercy Trees will take your breath away.” —Robin Antalek, author of The Summer We Fell Apart
			Heather Newton’s Under the Mercy Trees tells the poignant and unforgettable story of a man forced to face his troubled past when he returns to his hometown in the mountains of North Carolina following the disappearance of his brother.
			Thirty years ago, Martin Owenby came to New York City with dreams of becoming a writer. Now his existence revolves around cheap Scotch and weekend flings with equally damaged men. When he learns that his older brother, Leon, has gone missing, he must return to the Owenby farm in Solace Fork, North Carolina, to assist in the search. But that means facing a past filled with regrets, the family that never understood him, the girl whose heart he broke, and the best friend who has faithfully kept the home fires burning. As the mystery surrounding Leon's disappearance deepens, so too does the weight of decades-long unresolved differences and unspoken feelings—forcing Martin to deal with the hardest lessons about home, duty, and love.
			Under the Mercy Trees adds the name Heather Newton to a sterling list of acclaimed authors in the Southern literary tradition that already includes Reynolds Price, Kaye Gibbons, Jill McCorkle, Clyde Edgerton, and Tom Franklin
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>77</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Ingredients of Love</Title>
		<Author>Nicolas Barreau	</Author>
		<Cover>cover_77</Cover>
		<Text>
			The day begins like any other Saturday for beautiful Parisian restaurateur Aurélie Bredin, until she wakes up to find her apartment empty - her boyfriend gone off with another woman.
			Heartbroken, Aurelie walks the streets of Paris in the rain, finally seeking refuge in a little bookshop in the Ile St. Louis, where she's drawn to a novel titled The Smiles of Women by obscure English author Robert Miller. She buys it and takes it home, but when she begins to read she's astonished: The Smiles of Women can't possibly be about her restaurant … about her. Except, it is.
			Flattered and curious to know more, Aurélie knows she must get in touch with the reclusive Mr Miller, but it proves to be a daunting task. His French publishers seem determined to keep his identity secret, and while the Editor-in-Chief André Chabanais is happy to give Aurelie his time, he seems mysteriously unwilling to help her find her author. Is Robert Miller really so shy, or is there something that André isn't telling Aurélie?
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>78</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Secret Paris Cinema Club</Title>
		<Author>Nicolas Barreau</Author>
		<Cover>cover_78</Cover>
		<Text>
			Alain Bonnard, the owner of a small art cinema in Paris, is a dyed-in-the-wool nostalgic. In his Cinéma Paradis there are no buckets of popcorn, no XXL colas, no Hollywood blockbusters. Alain holds firm to his principles of quality - to show films that bring dreams to life, make people fall in love. And Alain would do anything for his clientele - particularly the mysterious woman in the red coat who, for some time now, has turned up every Wednesday and always sits in row seventeen. What could her story be?
			Finally one evening Alain plucks up courage to invite the unknown beauty to dinner. But just as the most tender of love stories is getting under way, something happens that turns Alain's life upside down, shoving his little cinema unexpectedly into the public eye. So when the woman in the red coat suddenly vanishes from his life, the cinema owner can't help but wonder if it is more than a coincidence. Taking matters into his own hands, Alain sets off in search of the stranger he has come to love - roll the opening credits for a timeless cinematic romance worthy of the Parisian silver screen!
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>79</DOCNO>
		<Title>Favorite</Title>
		<Author>Karen McQuestion</Author>
		<Cover>cover_79</Cover>
		<Text>
			Five years have passed since sixteen-year-old Angie Favorite’s mother disappeared without a trace. Since that day, Angie has managed to go through the motions of everyday life—until the summer morning when she’s abducted from a mall parking lot. Angie narrowly escapes, and her attacker is arrested, but he takes his life in jail before he can offer an explanation for his crime. When his mother contacts Angie, begging forgiveness on her son’s behalf, the girl agrees to meet with her in hopes of finding answers to the seemingly random attack. But when she arrives at the family’s massive estate, she is overcome by an unshakeable sense of foreboding...
			Part thriller, part coming-of-age tale, Favorite is an engrossing young adult novel in which nothing—and no one—is as it seems.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>80</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Long Way Home</Title>
		<Author>Karen McQuestion</Author>
		<Cover>cover_80</Cover>
		<Text>
			Four women bound by chance take the trip of a lifetime in this heartwarming novel by bestselling author Karen McQuestion.
			For Wisconsinites Marnie, Laverne, and Rita, life isn't working out so well. Each is biding time, waiting for something better, something to transport them out of what their lives have recently become. And then there’s Jazzy: bubbly, positive, and happy even though she hears voices of the departed. Brought together by a chance meeting, the women decide to join Marnie on a road trip from Wisconsin to Las Vegas where she intends to reunite with Troy, the boy she raised as her own—and who she’s been separated from since her boyfriend’s death. Little do they know that as the road trip unfolds, so will their lives—in directions they never anticipated. Humorous, heartwarming, and bittersweet, the journey has something special in store for each woman.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>81</DOCNO>
		<Title>Regarding Ducks and Universes</Title>
		<Author>Neve Maslakovic</Author>
		<Cover>cover_81</Cover>
		<Text>
			On a foggy Monday in 1986, the universe suddenly, without warning, bifurcated. Fast-forward to 35 years later: Felix Sayers is a culinary writer living in San Francisco of Universe A who spends his days lunching at Coconut Café and dreaming of penning an Agatha Christie-style mystery. But everything changes when his Aunt Henrietta dies, leaving Felix a photograph of his father and himself--dated ten days before Felix was born. It can only mean one thing: Felix has an 'alter' in Universe B. Panicked that his mystery novel may exist already, Felix crosses to San Francisco B and proceeds to flagrantly violate the rules of both worlds by snooping around his alter's life. But when he narrowly escapes a hit-and-run, it becomes clear that someone knows he's crossed over... and whoever it is isn't happy about it. Now Felix must uncover the truth about his alter, the events of one Monday, and a wayward rubber duck before his time in both worlds runs out.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>82</DOCNO>
		<Title>Rite of Wrongs</Title>
		<Author>Mica Stone</Author>
		<Cover>cover_82</Cover>
		<Text>
			Honor thy father and thy mother.
			Stress is a constant in Detective Miriam Rome’s life due to her heavy caseload. Now she’s facing an especially gruesome crime: a pediatrician’s wife has been brutally murdered, and a Bible verse written in her blood is found at the scene. As the tranquil city of Union Park, Texas, is left reeling, Detective Rome pursues every possible lead in her search for the murderer.
			When a second slaying—and second bloody quote—seems to confirm that a serial killer is at large, Rome is forced to turn to her former partner for his particular insight. Father Augustine Treece had walked away from police work, but now Rome’s request has drawn him back into the grisly world he thought he’d left behind.
			Working to stay ahead of the murders, Detective Rome and Father Treece must forgive their past to protect the next victim…a task that tests Rome’s limits when the killer hits too close to home.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>83</DOCNO>
		<Title>No Peace for the Damned (Magnolia Kelch Book 1)</Title>
		<Author>Megan Powell </Author>
		<Cover>cover_83</Cover>
		<Text>
			Magnolia Kelch is no stranger to pain. Beautiful and powerful, she’s spent her entire life at the mercy of her sadistic father and the rest of the Kelch clan, who have tortured her and tested the limits of her powers. After one particularly heinous night that leaves Magnolia nearly dead, she finally sees her chance for escape…
			But this first taste of freedom is short-lived when she collides with Thirteen, head of the Network—a secret organization dedicated to fighting supernatural criminals—who recruits her into the group. Even as she’s coming to grips with this new life and the horrific memories that still haunt her, she’s conflicted by her growing attraction to fellow team member Theo and the emergence of new, untested abilities. After months of grueling training, her loyalty to the team is tested when she learns her target is the Network’s most wanted: the Kelch family.
			Revenge may course through her veins, but so does the blood of the Kelches. And opposing her family may cost her the thing she treasures most. After all, Magnolia is still a Kelch. And the Kelch are damned.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>84</DOCNO>
		<Title>No Love for the Wicked (Magnolia Kelch Book 2)</Title>
		<Author>Megan Powell</Author>
		<Cover>cover_84</Cover>
		<Text>
			It’s taken six months, but supernaturally gifted Magnolia Kelch finally seems to have her surging powers under control. Then she arrives home to find a group of strangers in her beloved farmhouse, and that control is immediately put to the test. Magnolia quickly learns that her “guests” are actually part of the Network—not from the task force headed by her mentor, Thirteen, but a second group, led by British agent Colin St. Pierre.
			Unfortunately, Theo, a Network agent who shares an intimate connection with Magnolia, doesn’t trust Colin as a new commander. When team missions collide, Magnolia finds herself in the middle of Network infighting, asking herself who among those closest to her truly has her best interests at heart.
			But an even greater threat lies on the horizon. Intent on tracking down the source of Magnolia’s powers, a familiar enemy resurfaces with a plan—one that is far more sinister than the Network has ever seen.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>85</DOCNO>
		<Title>Mercury Rises</Title>
		<Author>Robert Kroese </Author>
		<Cover>cover_85</Cover>
		<Text>
			Mercury Rises: The explosive sequel to Mercury Falls!
			Jaded religion reporter Christine Temetri and Mercury, a renegade angel, have just thwarted two diabolical plots to destroy the world. But their work isn’t finished yet: mysterious powers outranking even the Heavenly bureaucracy seem intent on keeping the Apocalypse on track. While the world is plagued by natural disasters and nations prepare for war, crazed billionaire Horace Finch plots to use a secret device hidden beneath the African desert to discover the deepest secrets of the Universe—even if he has to destroy the Universe to do it. Meanwhile, unassuming FBI investigator Jacob Slater tries in vain to find a rational explanation for the mysterious destruction of downtown Anaheim—a quest that ultimately brings him to Kenya, where he meets Christine and Mercury. Together, the three must stop Finch from activating the device and tearing reality to pieces. Uproarious and wildly entertaining, Mercury Rises proves that the devil is in the details!
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>86</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Wet Nurse's Tale</Title>
		<Author>Erica Eisdorfer</Author>
		<Cover>cover_86</Cover>
		<Text>
			A debut novel set in Victorian England with a delightfully cheeky heroine who will have everyone talking. 
			Susan Rose is not your average Victorian heroine. She's promiscuous, lovable, plump, and scheming. Luckily for Susan, her big heart is covered by an equally big bosom, and her bosom is her fortune- for Susan becomes a professional wet nurse, like her mother before her, and she makes it her business to know all the intrigues and scandals that the upper crust would prefer to keep to themselves. 
			When her own child is caught up in a family scandal, Susan must use all of her street smarts to rescue her baby from the powerful mistress of the house. The scheme she weaves is bold and daring, and could spell ruin if she fails-but Susan Rose has no intention of failing.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>87</DOCNO>
		<Title>Need to Know</Title>
		<Author>Karen Cleveland</Author>
		<Cover>cover_87</Cover>
		<Text>
			Vivian Miller. High-powered CIA analyst, happily married to a man she adores, mother of four beautiful children. Until the moment she makes a shocking discovery that makes her question everything she believes. She thought she knew her husband inside and out. But now she wonders if it was all a lie. How far will she go to learn the truth?  And does she really.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>88</DOCNO>
		<Title>Flight of the Sparrow: A Novel of Early America</Title>
		<Author>Amy Belding Brown</Author>
		<Cover>cover_88</Cover>
		<Text>
			A historical novel based on the life of Mary Rowlandson
			“An authentic drama of Indian captivity…A compelling, emotionally gripping tale.”—Eliot Pattison, author of the Mystery of Colonial America series
			She suspects that she has changed too much to ever fit easily into English society again. The wilderness has now become her home. She can interpret the cries of birds. She has seen vistas that have stolen away her breath. She has learned to live in a new, free way.... 
			Massachusetts Bay Colony, 1676. Even before Mary Rowlandson was captured by Indians on a winter day of violence and terror, she sometimes found herself in conflict with her rigid Puritan community. Now, her home destroyed, her children lost to her, she has been sold into the service of a powerful woman tribal leader, made a pawn in the ongoing bloody struggle between English settlers and native people. Battling cold, hunger, and exhaustion, Mary witnesses harrowing brutality but also unexpected kindness. To her confused surprise, she is drawn to her captors’ open and straightforward way of life, a feeling further complicated by her attraction to a generous, protective English-speaking native known as James Printer. All her life, Mary has been taught to fear God, submit to her husband, and abhor Indians. Now, having lived on the other side of the forest, she begins to question the edicts that have guided her, torn between the life she knew and the wisdom the natives have shown her.
			Based on the compelling true narrative of Mary Rowlandson, Flight of the Sparrow is an evocative tale that transports the reader to a little-known time in early America and explores the real meanings of freedom, faith, and acceptance.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>89</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Birth House</Title>
		<Author>Ami McKay</Author>
		<Cover>cover_89</Cover>
		<Text>
			The Birth House is the story of Dora Rare, the first daughter to be born in five generations of the Rare family. As a child in an isolated village in Nova Scotia, she is drawn to Miss Babineau, an outspoken Acadian midwife with a gift for healing and a kitchen filled with herbs and folk remedies. During the turbulent first years of World War I, Dora becomes the midwife's apprentice. Together, they help the women of Scots Bay through infertility, difficult labors, breech births, unwanted pregnancies and even unfulfilling sex lives.
			But when Gilbert Thomas, a brash medical doctor, comes to Scots Bay with promises of fast, painless childbirth, some of the women begin to question Miss Babineau's methods—and after Miss Babineau's death, Dora is left to carry on alone. In the face of fierce opposition, she must summon all of her strength to protect the birthing traditions and wisdom that have been passed down to her.
			Filled with details that are as compelling as they are surprising—childbirth in the aftermath of the Halifax Explosion, the prescribing of vibratory treatments to cure hysteria and a mysterious elixir called Beaver Brew—Ami McKay has created an arresting and unforgettable portrait of the struggles that women faced to have control of their own bodies and to keep the best parts of tradition alive in the world of modern medicine.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>90</DOCNO>
		<Title>Bound</Title>
		<Author>Sally Cabot Gunning</Author>
		<Cover>cover_90</Cover>
		<Text>
			Alice Cole spent her first seven years living in two smoky, crowded rooms in London with her family. But a new home and a better life waited in the colonies, or so her father promised—a bright dream that turned to ashes when her brothers and mother took ill and died during the arduous voyage. Arriving in New England unable to meet the added expenses incurred by their misfortunes at sea, her father bound Alice into servitude to pay his debts.
			By the age of fifteen, Alice can barely remember the time when she was not a servant to John Morton and his daughter, Nabby. Though work fills her days, life with the Mortons is pleasant; Mr. Morton calls Alice his "sweet, good girl," and Nabby, only three years older, is her friend, companion, and now newly married, her mistress.
			But Nabby's marriage is not happy, and soon Alice is caught up in its storm; seeing nothing ahead but her own destruction, she defies her new master and the law and runs away to Boston. There she meets a sympathetic widow named Lyddie Berry and her lawyer companion, Eben Freeman. Frightened and alone, Alice impulsively stows away on their ship to Satucket on Cape Cod, where the Widow Berry offers Alice a bed and a job making cloth in support of the new boycott of British wool and linen.
			At Widow Berry's, Alice believes her old secret is safe, until it becomes threatened by a new one. As the days pass, the political and the personal stakes rise and intertwine, ultimately setting off a chain of events that will force Alice to question all she thought she knew. Bound by law, society, and her own heart, Alice soon discovers that freedom—as well as gratitude, friendship, trust, and love—has a price far higher than any she ever imagined.
			Library Journal hailed Sally Gunning's previous novel, The Widow's War, as "historical fiction at its best." With Bound, this wonderfully talented writer returns to pre-Revolutionary New England and evokes a long-ago time filled with uncertainty, hardship, and promise.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>91</DOCNO>
		<Title>Page from a Tennessee Journal</Title>
		<Author>Francine Thomas Howard </Author>
		<Cover>cover_91</Cover>
		<Text>
			A family secret is the inspiration for Francine Thomas Howard's remarkable debut novel, set in 1913, that focuses on a white couple who own a rural Tennessee farm and an African-American husband and wife, sharecroppers who work their land.
			In the novel, Annalaura Welles is forced to become the mistress of landowner Alex McNaughton after her husband, John, abandons her and her children. But trouble ensues when McNaughton develops genuine feelings for her. A sexual relationship is culturally acceptable, but love is not.
			When John returns, Annalaura must make decisions that will preserve the lives of the main characters and a baby who's on the way. It's a story as suspenseful as it is rich in detail about the evolving relationships between blacks and whites and men and women in the rural south.
			Page From a Tennessee Journal is also of note because it's one of the first books to be offered by AmazonEncore, a publishing program from Amazon that includes books that may not catch the eye of traditional publishers. -- Carol Memmott, USA TODAY
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>92</DOCNO>
		<Title>Russell Wiley Is Out to Lunch</Title>
		<Author>Richard Hine</Author>
		<Cover>cover_92</Cover>
		<Text>
			Russell Wiley is in deep trouble. A media executive for the failing Daily Business Chronicle, his career is teetering on the brink of collapse, and his sexless marriage is fast approaching its expiration date. With his professional and personal lives floundering, it’s no wonder Russell is distracted, unhappy, and losing faith in himself. Making matters worse are his scheming boss, a hot-shot new consultant determined to see Russell ousted, and the beguiling colleague whose mere presence has a disconcerting effect on Russell’s starved libido. Disaster seems imminent…and that’s before he makes a careless mistake that could cost the paper millions. Russell realizes he must take drastic action if he is going to salvage his career, his love life, and what little remains of his self-respect. Sardonic, edgy, and true to life, this gripping novel offers an insider’s view into a newspaper's inner sanctum and the people who oil the wheels of the "old media" machine.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>93</DOCNO>
		<Title>Jennifer Johnson Is Sick of Being Married</Title>
		<Author>Heather McElhatton</Author>
		<Cover>cover_93</Cover>
		<Text>
			No so terribly long ago, Heather McElhatton’s flawed, neurotic, yet lovable average American heroine Jennifer Johnson was sick of being single. Now Jennifer Johnson is Sick of Being Married. The author who brought us the wildly popular Pretty Little Mistakes now favors readers with the next delectably eventful chapter in Jennifer’s life, as her new fairy tale marriage (to the wealthy son of a department store tycoon) hits a serious snag, thanks in no small part to a honeymoon-from-hell in a fundamentalist Christian compound and the prospect of a life of bizarre servitude to her devout mother-in-law’s church committee. This is outrageously funny, wonderfully edgy contemporary women’s fiction in the Helen Fielding and Sophie Kinsella mode that anyone who has ever laughed at the raunchy humor of Sarah Silverman or Chelsea Handler is going to love.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>94</DOCNO>
		<Title>You Don't Look Fat, You Look Crazy</Title>
		<Author>Ashley Longshore </Author>
		<Cover>cover_94</Cover>
		<Text>
			Carpe diem, bitches.” —Ashley Longshore
			Pour a glass of champagne, slip off your designer heels, pull up your big girl panties and enjoy pop-artist extraordinaire Ashley Longshore’s unapologetic, raw, and literally laugh-out-loud funny guide to living an “ambitchous” life.
			For Ashley Longshore, the path from reluctant Southern Belle to badass artist and aspiring mogul hasn’t always been a smooth one. As a reformed Trophy-Wife-in-Training, Ashley has overcome failure, healed heartbreak, and worked damn hard, all with her signature killer attitude, to conquer the art world one glittery pop-art masterpiece at a time.
			You Don’t Look Fat, You Look Crazy is a window into the world of Longshore’s irreverent, glamorous, and stunningly visual pop-art-filled life, where bedazzled flowers sit next to diamonds and Valium boxes, Jesus holds a black Amex and Wonder Woman dresses in Chanel. With tongue-in-cheek advice straight from her canvas, such as  “There’s No Crying At Bergdorf’s,” “Always Ask For More,” and “What Would Blue Ivy Do,” Ashley’s honesty and DGAF attitude will grab you by your Givenchy lapels and hit you across the face with the donut you promised yourself you wouldn’t eat.
			So be confident, grab life by the Birkins, embrace your “ambitchion,” and remember, you don’t look fat—you look crazy! 
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>95</DOCNO>
		<Title>Larry's Kidney: Being the True Story of How I Found Myself in China with My Black Sheep Cousin and His Mail-Order Bride, Skirting the Law to Get Him a Transplant--and Save His Life</Title>
		<Author>Daniel Asa Rose</Author>
		<Cover>cover_95</Cover>
		<Text>
			One of the funniest, most touching and bizarre nonfiction books I’ve read.”	
			—Boston Globe
			Larry’s Kidney is Daniel Asa Rose’s wild-and-crazy memoir about his trip to Beijing, China, to help his black-sheep cousin Larry receive an illegal kidney transplant, collect a mail-order bride, and stop a hit-man from killing their uncle. An O. Henry Prize winner,  a two-time recipient of PEN Fiction Awards, and a 2006 National Endowment for the Arts Literary Fellow, Rose has written “a surprisingly fun, and moving, book with resonance” (Chicago Tribune).
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>96</DOCNO>
		<Title>Something Missing</Title>
		<Author>Matthew Dicks</Author>
		<Cover>cover_96</Cover>
		<Text>
			"The story of an obsessive-compulsive housebreaker whose every waking moment is jam-packed with finicky clockwork ritual--the kind of intense micro-planning that might have made even Napoleon back off...Matthew Dicks has created an unforgettable character that will have you torn between wanting to throttle him--or adopt him." 
			--Alan Bradley, author of the New York Times bestselling Flavia de Luce novels
			A career criminal with OCD tendencies and a savant-like genius for bringing order to his crime scenes, Martin considers himself one of the best. After all, he’s been able to steal from the same people for years on end—virtually undetected. Of course, this could also be because of his unique business model—taking only items that will go unnoticed by the homeowner. After all, who would notice a missing roll of toilet paper here, a half-used bottle of maple syrup there, or even a rarely used piece of china buried deep within a dusty cabinet?
			Even though he's never met these homeowners, spending hours in their houses, looking through their photo albums and reading their journals, he feels like he knows them. So Martin decides to meddle more in their lives—playing the part of a rather odd guardian angel—even though it means breaking many of his neurotic rules. 
			In this hilarious, suspenseful and often profound novel about a man used to planning every second of his life, Martin comes to realize that life is much better lived on the edge (at least some of the time).
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>97</DOCNO>
		<Title>The Last to See Me</Title>
		<Author>M Dressler</Author>
		<Cover>cover_97</Cover>
		<Text>
			For readers of Lauren Oliver and Alice Sebold, a sophisticated, literary ghost story that reminds us the past is never, ever forgotten.
			In a small logging town in northern California, young Emma Rose Finnis was born and died. Now, no one remembers her hardworking life and her grand dreams--but she remembers. She remembers everything. Emma Rose is still here, one hundred years after her death . . . and she doesn't plan on leaving.
			But when a determined hunter arrives with instructions to "clean" Emma Rose out of her haunt, the stately Lambry mansion, death suddenly isn't the worst fate imaginable. Emma Rose refuses to be hounded from the only place she's ever found peace, even if it means waging a war on the living . . . and the dead.
			Lyrical and haunting, this spellbinding American ghost story alternates between Emma Rose's life and afterlife as the past and present become entwined in a compelling tale of loss, love and tenacity over a century in the making.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>98</DOCNO>
		<Title>My Absolute Darling</Title>
		<Author>Gabriel Tallent</Author>
		<Cover>cover_98</Cover>
		<Text>
			NSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER 
			LA TIMES BOOK PRIZE FINALIST
			NBCC JOHN LEONARD PRIZE FINALIST
			ONE OF THE NEW YORK TIMES'S MOST NOTABLE BOOKS OF 2017
			ONE OF THE WASHINGTON POST’S MOST NOTABLE BOOKS OF 2017
			ONE OF NPR’S ‘GREAT READS’ OF 2017
			A USA TODAY BEST BOOK OF THE YEAR
			AN AMAZON.COM BEST BOOK OF THE YEAR
			A BUSINESS INSIDER BEST BOOK OF THE YEAR
			"Impossible to put down." —NPR
			"A novel that readers will gulp down, gasping.” —The Washington Post
 			"The word 'masterpiece' has been cheapened by too many blurbs, but My Absolute Darling absolutely is one." —Stephen King
			A brilliant and immersive, all-consuming read about one fourteen-year-old girl's heart-stopping fight for her own soul.
			Turtle Alveston is a survivor. At fourteen, she roams the woods along the northern California coast. The creeks, tide pools, and rocky islands are her haunts and her hiding grounds, and she is known to wander for miles. But while her physical world is expansive, her personal one is small and treacherous: Turtle has grown up isolated since the death of her mother, in the thrall of her tortured and charismatic father, Martin. Her social existence is confined to the middle school (where she fends off the interest of anyone, student or teacher, who might penetrate her shell) and to her life with her father.
			Then Turtle meets Jacob, a high-school boy who tells jokes, lives in a big clean house, and looks at Turtle as if she is the sunrise. And for the first time, the larger world begins to come into focus: her life with Martin is neither safe nor sustainable. Motivated by her first experience with real friendship and a teenage crush, Turtle starts to imagine escape, using the very survival skills her father devoted himself to teaching her. What follows is a harrowing story of bravery and redemption. With Turtle's escalating acts of physical and emotional courage, the reader watches, heart in throat, as this teenage girl struggles to become her own hero—and in the process, becomes ours as well.
			Shot through with striking language in a fierce natural setting, My Absolute Darling is an urgently told, profoundly moving read that marks the debut of an extraordinary new writer.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>99</DOCNO>
		<Title>Repeat</Title>
		<Author>Neal Pollack</Author>
		<Cover>cover_99</Cover>
		<Text>
			Through strange metaphysical circumstances, failed screenwriter Brad Cohen finds himself caught in an infinite time loop, forced to relive the first forty years of his life again and again. Each “repeat,” Brad wakes up in the womb on what was supposed to be his fortieth birthday, with full knowledge of what’s come before. In various timelines, he becomes a successful political pundit, a game-show champion, a playboy, and a master manipulator of the stock market, but none of them seem to lead him out of his predicament. As he realizes he wants to break out of the loop and find the love of his life—the one he hadn’t appreciated the first time around—Brad tries, fails, and tries again to escape the eternal cycle of birth and rebirth. Repeat answers the question: If you could live half your life over, would you do things differently? Be careful what you wish for! Repeating is enough to drive a dude crazy.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
	<DOC>
		<DOCNO>100</DOCNO>
		<Title>All You Could Ask For</Title>
		<Author>Mike Greenberg</Author>
		<Cover>cover_100</Cover>		
		<Text>
			All You Could Ask For, debut novel by Mike Greenberg, cohost of ESPN's Mike and Mike in the Morning, is a tender and insightful story of friendship and love, heartbreak and renewal, played out in the lives of three unforgettable women.
			Brooke has been happily married to her college sweetheart for fifteen years. Even after the C-section, the dog poop, the stomach viruses and the coffee breath, Scott always winks at her in just the right moments. That is why, for her beloved, romantic, successful husband’s fortieth birthday, she is giving him pictures. Of herself. Naked.
			Newlywed Samantha learns of her husband’s cheating heart when she finds the goods on his computer.
			High-powered career woman Katherine works with heartbreaker Phillip, the man who hurt her early on in her career.          
			Brooke, Samantha, and Katherine don’t know each other, but their stories are about to intertwine in ways no one could have imagined.
			And all three are about to discover the power of friendship to conquer adversity, the satisfaction of unexpected delights, the incredible difference one human being can have on other lives--and that they have all they could ask for, as long as they have each other.
		</Text>
	</DOC>
</Collection>